好了,大家一起来吧
All right, everybody, come on.
到舞池中来
Out on the dance floor.
看看这幸福的一对
Oh ho ho! Look at the happy couple.
不得有异议
No exceptions.
都站起来
Up out of your chairs.
Whoo!
Yeah!
我能感觉到这里所有的快乐
Oh, I can feel all the happiness in here.
就是这样
All right!
看看他吧
Man, look at him go.
Go! Go!
如果我...
# If I #
我想知道你的名字...
# I get to know your name #
如果我...
# If I #
能查到你的私人电话,宝贝...
# Could trace your private number, baby #
我只知道对我来说...
# All I know is that to me #
你看起来非常令人愉快
# You look like you're lots of fun #
张开那爱的双手
# Open up them lovin' arms #
我需要爱,需要一些爱
# I want some, want some #
我目不转睛看着你
# I set my sights on you #
没有其他人会这样
# And no one else will do #
而且我...
# And I #
我要马上开始行动,宝贝
# I got to have my way now, baby #
我只知道对我来说...
# All I know is that to me #
你看起来非常令人愉快
# You look like you're lots of fun #
张开你爱的双手
# Open up them lovin' arms #
留意,我来了
# Watch out, here I come #
你让我团团转,宝贝,团团转...
# You spin me right round, baby, right round #
活象一张唱片,宝贝...
# Like a record, baby #
团团转,转,转
# Right round, round, round #
你让我团团转,宝贝,团团转...
# You spin me right round, baby, right round #
活象一张唱片,宝贝...
# Like a record, baby #
团团转,转,转
# Right round, round, round #
哪位给那孩子穿上裤子吧
Hey, somebody get some pants on that kid.
Whoo-hoo!
如果我...
# And I #
我要和你做朋友...
# I got to be your friend #
莫莉祖母,我是在对你说
Grandma Molly, I'm talking to you.
而且我...
# And I #
会高兴能接近哪怕一点点
# Would like to move in just a little bit closer #
我只知道对我来说...
# All I know is that to me #
你看起来非常令人愉快
# You look like you're lots of fun #
张开你爱的双手
# Open up your lovin' arms #
留意,我来了
# Watch out, here I come #
你让我团团转,宝贝,团团转...
# You spin me right round, baby, right round #
活象一张唱片,宝贝...
# Like a record, baby #
团团转,转,转
# Right round, round, round #
你让我团团转,宝贝,团团转...
# You spin me right round, baby, right round #
活象一张唱片,宝贝
# Like a record, baby, right... #
我需要你的爱
# I want your lo-o-o-o-o-ove #
# I want your love #
# O-o-o-o-o-ove #
马蒂叔叔
Uncle Morty!
Yeah!
我只知道对我来说...
# All I know is that to me #
你看起来非常令人愉快
# You look like you're lots of fun #
张开你爱的双手
# Open up your lovin' arms #
留意,我来了
# Watch out, here I come #
你让我团团转,宝贝,团团转...
# You spin me right round, baby, right round #
活象一张唱片,宝贝...
# Like a record, baby #
团团转,转,转
# Right round, round, round #
你让我团团转,宝贝,团团转...
# You spin me right round, baby, right round #
活象一张唱片,宝贝...
# Like a record, baby #
团团转,转,转
# Right round, round, round #
你让我团团转...
# You spin me round and round #
转呀转...
# And rounddddd #
非常好
Very nice.
Yeah.
你跳得很好,女士
Good job, lady. You were shakin'.
Whoo!
今天的精彩时刻即将来临
It is gonna be fun today.
伴郎将要上来说几句...
Now the best man's gonna come up here and say a few words...
让我们一起为新郎的兄长大卫鼓掌
so let's put our hands together for the groom's brother David.
Whoo!
All right, Dave.
Oof!
Whoa!
Um...
当我的兄弟哈罗德
when my brother Harold...
要求我做伴郎时...
asked me to be the best man at his wedding, I was like, "Whoa.
我欣然接受:"当然,伙计...
"Of course, man...
"因为你总是在我的身边"
"'cause you've always been there for me."
- Aww. - That's right.
例如我难受的时候...
Like when I was in rehab...
还有我找不到我的车的时候
and like the time I couldn't find my car.
Ha ha!
因为哈罗德总是值得信赖的
'Cause Harold, you know, he's always been the dependable one.
而我则是
I've always...
一无是处的,对吧,老爹?
been the screwed-up one. Right, Dad?
Ha ha.
"你为什么不能更象你兄弟一点?
"Why can't you be more like your brother?
"哈罗德从没惊扰过他的房东"
"Harold would never beat up his landlord."
他醉得象滩烂泥
He's drunk as shit.
Whoops.
但是...
But, uh...
有个意外的消息,老爹
a little news flash, Pop. Ha.
哈罗德并不那么完美
Harold ain't so perfect.
记得那次在波多黎各...
Remember that time in Puerto Rico...
我们勾搭上那两个...
when we picked up those two, uh...
我猜她们是妓女, 不过忘了是否付过钱
well, I guess they were prostitutes, but I don't remember paying.
感觉怎样呢?
OK, how 'bout that?
感觉怎样?
How 'bout that? Yeah. How 'bout it?
妙不可言
Terrific.
我也是人,老爹,去他妈的,我也是人
I'm a person, too, Pop, god damn it! I'm a person, too!
你是个白痴
You're a moron!
Ooh.
OK.
这就是伴郎,各位
The best man, everybody.
伴郎(直译为最好的男人)是比较好的男人
Best man. The better man.
Ooh!
Uh... hey...
我们在生活中都做过疯狂的事,所以...
we've all done crazy things in our life, so...
他弹起了吉他,很不错是吧?
He's playing the guitar now. Isn't that great?
-他弹得不赖 -不赖是吧?
- Ha ha ha. You're doing good. - Yeah? Sounds good?
因为我是世上最棒的吉他手
It's because I'm the best guitar player in the world.
自学成才
Yeah. Self-taught.
没上过课. 很感谢你,老爹
No lessons, thank you very much, Pop.
好了
All right.
一年内他们就会离婚
They'll be divorced in a year.
说得很好
Very good.
我想我们都知道, 当坠入爱河时...
I think, uh, we all know that when you fall in love...
空虚感会慢慢消失
the emptiness kind of drifts away.
这就是我要说的
That's all I'm talking about.
我这辈子也做过疯狂的事...
I've, uh, done some crazy things in my life, too...
但后来我遇见一位非常特别的女孩...
but then I met a very special girl...
一个下周我就要与她结婚的女孩
a girl who I'm actually marrying next week.
谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
所以我要说的是当你坠入爱河时...
So all I'm saying is that when you fall in love, like you guys...
空虚感会逐渐消逝... 因为你找到了生活的寄托...
the emptiness drifts away because you find something to live for:
彼此之间的
Each other.
就象我看到你们俩整天都在相互注视着...
And the way I've seen you two looking into each other's eyes all day long...
我能感觉到你们将会彼此扶持...
I can tell that you're gonna live for each other...
渡过你们的后半生
for the rest of your lives.
- Aww! - Yeah.
所以干杯吧
So cheers.
-干杯 -干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Yeah.
Whoo.
这是个很棒的婚礼歌手
That's a good wedding singer.
现在我代表哈罗德夫妇...
OK, well, now on behalf of Mr. And Mrs. Harold Veltri...
祝各位晚餐愉快
you guys have a nice dinner.
乔治将接替主唱的位置...
George Stitzer here's gonna take over on lead vocals...
来吧,乔治
so take it away, George.
给我时间...
# Give me time #
来认识我的罪过
# To realize my crime #
让我去爱并停留下来
# Let me love and stay #
老天
- Ugh. - Jesus.
真恐怖
Scary.
我跳着舞...
# I have danced #
我喜欢她
Ooh, I like her.
在你的眼中
# Inside your eyes #
爱要怎么...
# How can love #
变得真实?
# Be real? #
你真的想伤害我吗?
# Do you really want to hurt me... #
Good save, wedding singer.
干得漂亮
Good job.
山米,你怎么没把酒喝掉?怎么了?
Hey, Sammy, how come you're not out with your limo? What's up?
那个新女侍就是原因所在
That new waitress. That's what's up.
她有麻烦了 她就会碰上的
Is she in trouble. She's gonna get it...
可她还浑然不觉... 而我将要去找她的麻烦
and she doesn't even know it, and I'm gonna give it to her.
放松点,老兄,她是谁?
Ha. Take it easy, man. Who is she?
她是霍莉-沙利文的表妹
She's Holly Sullivan's cousin.
如果她象霍莉一半那么好对付...
If she's half as easy as Holly...
这个周末我就不开业了
I'll close this deal by the end of the week.
Oh! Ohh.
我看没那么乐观
Mmm, I don't think that's gonna happen.
拜托,她这是第一天上班
Oh, please. It's her first day.
总得给她们三个星期...
Always takes them at least three weeks...
来认识她们不能在工作时和任何人约会
to realize they shouldn't date anyone at work.
你乐于亲自来让他们
For some reason, you like being the guy...
认识这一点?
that helps them realize that, don't you?
是的,没错
Yes, I do.
你想学冯兹("老友记"中人物)那样是吧?
You want to be like Fonzie, don't you?
是的,没错
Yes, I do.
你有你的自由
You're on your way.
# Do you really want to hurt me? #
# Do you really want to make me cry? #
I like old Coke better than New Coke...
because it's old, and so am I.
# Don't turn around, oh-oh-oh #
Yes!
# Der Kommissar's in town #
请来份好排骨
Prime rib, please.
总是好排骨
More prime rib. Always the prime rib.
让他们吃鱼吧
Make them eat the fish.
安德雷,能给我三份排骨吗?
Andre, can I have three prime rib?
你的愿望就是我的使命,夫人
Your wish is my command, madame.
他怎么对你这么好?
How come he's so nice to you?
我在圣诞晚会让他看了我的乳房
I let him look at my boobs at the Christmas party last year.
算不上我最爽的半个小时...
Not my finest half-hour...
但从那之后这里成了最舒适的工作场所
but it's been a pleasant working environment ever since.
别想
No.
那么,头天上班感觉如何?
So, how's your first night going, cuz?
为婚礼服务让我意识到...
It's just that being at this wedding...
格伦从没订下过日期...
is making me realize that Glenn is never going to set a date...
而我戴上这戒指已经两年了...
and I've been wearing this ring for two years...
我自觉象个白痴
and I feel like an idiot.
知道你该怎么做吗?
Hey, you know what you must do?
放松
Relax.
别这么做
Go to it.
Huh?
# Ja! Ja! Ja! #
我觉得上这来和他套近乎真是愚蠢
I just feel stupid for moving here to be closer to him.
你该休息一下,到后面去透透气
OK, I think you need a break. Go out back and get some air.
我会料理你的桌子
I'll cover your tables.
你还好吧?
- You OK? - Huh?
-想吐吗? -对
- You going to throw up? - Yeah.
跟我来,伙计
Come with me, man.
# Give me time #
怎么回事?
What?
到了.到了
Here we go. Here we go.
来吧
Here we go. Come on. Come on.
You got it.
就是这了
There. Hey.
他是你的朋友?
Is he a friend of yours?
我?不是 我不能让他的家人
Me? No, no. Actually, I couldn't let him do it...
看到他这样
in front of his family.
Wow.
真高兴能见到这一幕
Well, I'm glad I got to see it.
-吐完了吗? -好了
- OK. You all through? - Yeah.
在你下次喝酒之前你会不会等上几年?
Going to wait a few years before you drink again?
当然
Yeah.
好了,记住,酒精就等于呕吐...
All right, remember... alcohol equals puke...
等于又臭又脏,等于没人喜欢你
equals smelly mess equals nobody likes you.
让我逮着了
Hey, no, I... I got it from here.
知道吗?你走这边...
No, actually, you know what? You go this way...
而你走这边 这样最好
and you go this way. It's for the best.
没事了,小心点 回头见
It's all right. Take it easy. See you later.
睡一觉就好了,伙计
Sleep it off, pal. All right.
嘿,知道吗,歌手?
Hey, you know, wedding singer?
A-whoo!
OK.
-你也在喝酒吗? -不
- Are you drinking, too? - No.
是可乐
It's Coca-Cola.
你肯定可乐里没加朗姆酒?
Are you sure? There's no rum in that Coca-Cola?
我可不是酒鬼...
I'm not a big drinker...
如果是的话,我会比那孩子吐得更多
and if it was, I'd be puking in there more than that kid.
我可不认为有人能比那孩子吐得更多
Oh, I don't think anybody could puke more than that kid.
我想我看到吐出了一只靴子
I think I saw a boot come out of him.
你是那个婚礼歌手
You're the wedding singer.
你好,我是罗比
Yeah. How you doing? I'm Robbie.
我叫茱莉娅
I'm Julia.
下周我还要在你的婚礼上做招待
I'm actually waitressing at your wedding next week.
真不错
Cool.
你有一只漂亮的戒指
That's a beautiful ring you have there.
你也快结婚了吗?
Are you getting married, too?
说实话,我不知道他有多认真...
Actually, I don't know how serious the guy is...
送我戒指的那个人
who gave this to me.
我感觉象是注定要这星球上独自流浪
Right now, I feel like I'm doomed to wander the planet alone forever.
哦,不
Oh, no.
象"不可思议的绿巨人"一样吗?
Kind of like the Incredible Hulk, huh?
对...
Yeah...
只不过我不会帮助别人
only I'm not helping people.
不对,因为我在里面看到你了
That's not true, because I saw you inside.
你在帮助别人
You were helping people.
你给他们拿鱼,咖啡和餐叉
You were giving them fish and coffee and forks.
没有餐叉人们无法进食
People can't eat without forks.
没有鱼他们就不能喝酒
And they can't drink without a fish.
没错,这意味着什么呢?
That's right. I think... What does that mean?
我不知道,你把我弄糊涂变回绿巨人了
I don't know. You lost me back at the Hulk.
Hey.
罗比,你最好回里面去
Hey, Robbie, you better get back in there.
他们开始哄乔治了
They're starting to turn on George.
-坐下 -你个混蛋
- Sit down! - You suck!
你个混蛋
You suck!
他得学首新歌才行
He's got to learn a new song.
很高兴认识你
But, uh, OK, well, it was nice to meet you.
也很高兴认识你 如果我结婚的话...
It was nice meeting you, too. And if I do ever get married...
也许会请你在婚礼上唱歌
maybe you'll sing at my wedding.
哦,老天,这可是笔生意
Oh, man. It's a deal.
保重
- OK. - OK, take care.
爱...
# There was love #
Yeah.
环绕在周围...
- # All around # - Nice.
但我从没...
# But I never #
听到它歌唱
# Heard it singing #
很好
Very nice.
不,我从没...
# No, I never #
一点也没听到...
# Heard it at all #
非常好
Pretty.
直到有了
# 'Til there was #
你
# You #
进步很多了
Much better.
你会在你们的五十周年晚会上
Man, you're going to blow everybody away...
让所有人都陶醉
at your fiftieth anniversary party.
如果我能一点不错地唱给弗兰克听...
If I sing to Frank without making any mistakes...
他就会知道我有多努力...
he would know how hard I've worked...
还有这么多年后我仍然多么的爱他
and how much I still love him after all these years.
我希望今后的五十年...
I hope fifty years from now...
琳达和我会象你俩一样幸福
Linda and I are as happy as you two guys.
你们会的
Oh, you will be.
幸福会来到你们家里
It runs in your family.
你天生浪漫,象你父亲一样
You're a born romantic, just like your father was.
是吗?
Yeah?
我知道他们明天会在天上看着你
I know they'll be looking down on you tomorrow.
希望如此
I hope so.
你紧张吗?
Are you nervous?
实际上没那么紧张,知道吗?
I'm actually not that nervous, you know?
我总是参加婚礼,会很有意思的
I'm around weddings all the time. It's going to be fun.
我不是指婚礼
Oh, not about the wedding...
是指新婚之夜
about the wedding night.
将是你第一次做爱对吗?
Will this be your first time with intercourse?
Uh...
用不着害羞
Well... no, don't be ashamed.
我结婚时并不是处女
You know, when I got married, I wasn't a virgin.
已经和八个男人上过床
I already had intercourse with eight men.
实际上我想知道的不是这些
You know, that's actually something I don't want to know about.
在当时是很多了
That was a lot back then.
和现在的两百个一样
That would be like 200 today.
五点了,我该走了
Yeah. Uh, it's 5:00. I'm going to get going.
你的酬劳
Oh, but your payment.
我的酬劳,我可以带走吗?
My payment. Uh... can I get it to go?
你真是个可爱的小伙儿...
Oh, you're such a sweet boy...
让我这老太婆用肉丸作酬劳
letting an old woman pay you with meatballs.
它们味道很好
Oh, yeah, well, they taste so good...
我是在敲诈你呢
it's like I'm ripping you off, Rosie.
我没有干净的塑料袋
I don't have any clean tupperware.
那干脆下次再说
All right, well, definitely next time, OK?
别傻了,快把手伸出来
Don't be silly. Now hold out your hands.
-你想-- -伸出来
- You want to... - Yeah. Do it.
OK.
真棒
Oh. Cool.
太感谢了
- Thanks a lot. - Oh.
快,拜托...
Now, please...
咬上一口,好让我看到你享用它
take a bite so that I can watch you enjoy.
这是我最喜欢的
That's my favorite part.
好吧,我就吃右手这个
OK. Well... I'll go with the right one.
看样子很好吃
Heh heh. That looks good.
这是个很棒的肉丸
That's a good meatball. That's a good meatball.
现在...
Oh! Now...
听我说,罗比-哈特
listen to me, Robbie Hart.
你会成为一个好丈夫
You're going to be a fine husband.
但愿如此,露茜,谢谢你
Well, I hope so, Rosie. Thank you.
我得走了
OK, well, I'm going to leave.
婚礼上见,好吗?
I'll see you at the wedding, all right?
谢谢你来带我吃午饭
Well, thank you for coming in and taking me to lunch.
看那照片上的女孩,看到没有?
Look at the picture of that girl. See that?
你比那女孩可爱多了...
You're a lot prettier than that girl...
而她就要结婚了
and she's getting married.
可爱和结婚有什么关系?
What does pretty have to do with getting married?
密切相关,你应该结婚...
Everything. You got to get married...
在你的腰变粗和脸上长毛之前...
before your hips start spreading and you get facial hair...
这个,顺便说一下, 是遗传自你父亲的母亲
which, by the way, comes from your father's mother.
就象大酒瓶,老天啊
Looks like Magnum, P.I., for God's sake.
我没法让格伦定下日期
Well, I can't make Glenn set a date.
Well...
你会反感这个主意...
you're going to hate this idea...
但我觉得你该考虑来个假怀孕
but I think you should consider a fake pregnancy.
我下车了
I'm exiting the car.
这只是个达到目的的方法
Look, it's just a means to an end.
五年后他会因此而感谢你
Believe me, in five years, he'll thank you for it.
也许我们该打电话给她
Perhaps we should call her.
Uh...
也许她的化妆和衣着遇上了麻烦
she's probably got a make-up problem or her dress or something.
我了解她,她喜欢自己看上去是最佳状态
I know her. She likes to look her best. It'll be OK.
嘿,姐姐
- Robs? - Hey, sis.
嗨,罗比
Hi, Robs.
我刚和琳达的妈妈通过电话
I just got off the phone with Linda's mom.
琳达不在那,但...
Linda's not there, but...
有张留言条
there was a note.
留言条?
A note?
一切都正常吧?
Everything all right?
是的,她很好
Yeah, she's OK.
大概意思就是... 琳达...
It basically indicated that Linda was...
今天不会来
not coming today.
那么,是个不好的留言了
So, it was a bad note.
她有说为什么吗?
Did she say why?
我很抱歉,亲爱的
I am so sorry, honey.
没什么
It's OK.
想听我说点什么吗?
You want me to say something?
不
No.
等我一会儿
Just give me a second.
我很快就回来
I'Il... I'll be right back.
哦,我的天,她没有出现
Oh, my God, she's not showing up.
别担心
Don't worry, man.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's going to be all right.
没事的
It's OK. It's OK.
不!
No!
哦,上帝!
Oh, God!
她走了!
She's gone!
# Come on, it's a nice day #
# For a white wedding #
你抓不到我的
You can't catch me!
我要抓住你把你切开
I'm going to get you and chop you up!
能别再说废话吗?拜托
Can we turn this crap off, please?
没错,罗比,你该发泄出来
That's right, Robbie. You have to let it out, man.
-发泄什么? -你的情绪
- Let what out? - Your feelings.
为那可鄙的贱货今天对你所做的
You know, about what that lousy bitch did to you today.
别这么说她,因为我们会回到一起...
Don't call her that, because we're going to get back together...
然后你我之间会出现不妥...
and then there's going to be weirdness between you and me...
所以等着瞧吧
so just watch it.
我为你做了这个,罗比舅舅
I made this for you, Uncle Robbie.
谢谢,弗雷迪-克雷格
Oh, thanks, Freddy Krueger.
这不算很好
That's not nice.
但是很有创意
Very creative, though.
回锅炉房去吧
Go back to the boiler room.
我只希望知道她在哪,你们知道吗?
I just wish I knew where she was, you know?
他受的打击太大了
Man, he's taking it pretty bad.
他的举止就象个真正的机器人...
I mean, he's acting like a real robot...
或僵尸之类的
a zombie or something.
从三年级开始他就想要结婚
He's been wanting to get married since the third grade.
可以理解,当爸爸妈妈去世时
It makes sense. That's when Mom and Dad died.
他就想有个自己的家
He wants to start a family of his own.
看看蛋糕
Hey, check out the cake.
上面只有一个小新郎
There's only a little groom on top.
Mmm.
# Look for somethin' left in this world #
# Start again #
你迟到了
Hey. You're late.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我只是做不到
I just couldn't do it.
好吧...
Well...
如果你需要多点时间,我可以等
if you need some more time, I guess I can wait.
不,我不需要更多时间,罗比
No, I don't need more time, Robbie.
我没想过要嫁给你
I don't ever want to marry you.
知道吗,那个消息...
Jeez, you know, that information...
在昨天告诉我也许会好一点
might have been a little more useful to me yesterday.
早几天我和朋友聊过...
I've been talking to my friends the last couple of days...
原来如此
Oh, here it comes.
我想我意识到了是什么困扰着我
And I think I figured out what's been bothering me.
我爱的不是现在的罗比
I'm not in love with Robbie now.
我爱的是六年前的罗比...
I'm in love with Robbie six years ago...
罗比,"最后通牒"的主唱...
Robbie, the lead singer of Final Warning...
是我习惯从前排看你的时候...
when I used to come and watch you from the front row...
穿着弹力裤...
in your spandex pants...
敞着丝衬衣的钮扣...
your silk shirt unbuttoned...
象大卫-李-罗斯一样拍着麦克风
licking the microphone like David Lee Roth.
我还留着弹力裤,我现在就去穿上
I still got the spandex. I'll put them on right now.
关键是,今早我醒来...
The point is, I woke up this morning...
并意识到我将要嫁给一个婚礼歌手
and I realized I'm about to marry a wedding singer.
我从没离开过里奇菲尔德
I am never going to leave Ridgefield.
你为什么要离开里奇菲尔德?
Why do you need to leave Ridgefield?
我们在这长大,所有的朋友都在这
We grew up here. All our friends are here.
这里是组建家庭的好地方
It's the perfect place to raise a family.
是啊, 和五个孩子住在你姐姐的地下室...
Oh, yeah. Living in your sister's basement with five kids...
当你在每个周末结束最多
while you're off every weekend doing wedding gigs...
每场60美元的婚礼演出时?
at a whopping sixty bucks a pop?
再说一次...
Once again...
可以在昨天就提醒我注意
things that could have been brought to my attention yesterday!
事实是我们很久以前就分开了
The fact is, we grew apart a long time ago.
Mm-mmm.
你想结婚,不在乎是和谁
You just wanted to get married so badly, you didn't care to who.
不是的,我爱你
That's not true. I love you.
到这来,我想和你共渡我的下半生
Come here. I want to spend the rest of my life with you.
嘿,琳达
Hey, Linda.
你是个贱货
You're a bitch.
谢谢,佩蒂,回房里去
Thanks, Petey. Go back to the house.
他也许有"秽语综合症"
He... He might have Tourette's syndrome.
我们正在观察他
We're looking into it.
我得走了
I got to go.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
# 99 luftballons... #
Aah!
-格伦 -别太紧张
- Glenn! - Don't be so jumpy.
送给你
These are for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
真漂亮
They're beautiful.
我还有东西要送给你
I have something else for you.
两张去拉斯维加斯的机票?
Two airplane tickets to Las Vegas?
# Da dum de dum, da dum de dum #
哦,我的天,格伦
Oh, my God, Glenn! Oh, my God!
我知道你想定下日期...
I know you wanted to set a date...
所以我去旅行社安排了一下
so I went to the travel agent, and I set it.
格伦,我太爱你了 可拉斯维加斯?我想...
Glenn, I love you so much, but Las Vegas? I thought...
茱莉,那是世上的浪漫之都
Jules, it's the romance capital of the world.
我不想要太大的婚礼...
I just don't want a big wedding...
数以百计我们不认识的人...
you know, hundreds of people we don't know...
到场只是为了几杯酒...
that are just there for the free drinks...
和想吃就吃的自助餐
and all-you-can-eat buffet.
他们也可以去维加斯
They might as well be in Vegas.
好吧
OK.
就拉斯维加斯吧,那里会很不错
Las Vegas it is, and it'll be great.
茱莉...
Jules...
你不会象其他女孩一样吧?
are you going to do the girl thing?
假装开心
You're going to act happy...
但心里在生气?
and you're going to be pouting on the inside?
不,我很开心
No. I'm happy.
那就好
All right.
我们就在这结婚
Let's get married here.
我知道这是你想要的
I know that's what you want.
谢谢你,格伦
Thank you, Glenn.
谢谢你
Thank you.
总之这对你来说更重要
It's more important to you anyway.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我保证会给你最美的婚礼...
And I promise I will give you the most beautiful wedding...
而且会让你很开心
and even you'll have a good time.
Mm-hmm.
# Pass the dutchie on the left-hand side #
# It a-gonna burn #
# Give me the music, make me jump and prance #
# It a-go done #
# Give me the music, make me rock in the dance #
# You play it on the radio #
# And so me say we a-go hear it on the stereo... #
他最好的朋友是该出现了
Hey, it's about time his best friend showed up.
那么,他怎么样?
So, how's he doing?
不知道
I don't know, man.
事后他一直呆在地下室
He's been down in the basement since it happened...
已经五天了
five days now.
我想他有点心理障碍...
I think he's having some kind of a mental situation...
得有个过渡期
you know, an episode or something.
没错
All right.
# I said, pass the dutchie #
帮帮忙吧,我可不想作为
Hey, you better do something, because I don't want to be known...
本镇死脑筋的姐夫而为人熟知
as the brother-in-law of the town nut job.
我的麻烦够多了
I got enough problems already.
妈的,我洒了自己一身的水
Oh, shit, I got water all over myself.
# I would do most anything #
# To get you back by my side #
# But I just keep on laughing... #
喂?
Hello?
罗比
Hey, Robbie.
你还好吧?
You all right?
# Boys don't cry #
这被单真软,是Downy牌的吗?
Hey, these sheets are soft. You use Downy?
不
No.
都是Tempa-Cheer牌
All Tempa-Cheer.
可以在任何水温下洗涤...
You can wash your clothes at any temperature...
都不会褪色染色
and the colors don't run together.
-真的? -是的,让我自个儿呆着吧
- Really? - Yeah. Now leave me alone.
你得回去工作
You have to go back to work.
那里会有超过一百个喝醉的姑娘...
You know there's going to be over a hundred drunk girls...
在今晚的婚礼上
at this wedding tonight.
我帮不上任何人了
I've got nothing to offer anybody.
从高中起我就一事无成
I haven't done jack shit since high school.
哪个女孩会要嫁给我呢?
Why would any girl ever marry me?
嫁给你?
Marry you?
我只是想找人陪你玩玩罢了
I'm just trying to get someone to play with your ding-dong.
假日...
# Holiday #
庆祝...
# Celebrate #
假日...
# Holiday #
庆祝...
# Celebrate #
如果我们有个假日...
# If we took a holiday #
# Ooh, yeah, ooh, yeah #
花些时间来庆祝吧...
# Took some time to celebrate #
来吧,让我们庆祝
# Come on, let's celebrate #
只不过失去生命中的一天...
# Just one day out of life #
假日...
# Holiday #
那将会...
# It would be #
那将会非常美好
# It would be so nice #
所有人都在传言
# Everybody spread the word #
# Come on #
我住在我姐姐的地下室
# I live in my sister's basement #
# Come on #
他的心都碎了
He just had his heart broken.
为什么他会想回来工作呢?
Why would he even think about coming back to work?
我不知道
I don't know.
庆祝
# Celebrate #
你们完成了一个好的开始
You guys are off to a great start, don't you think?
我是说,辛蒂出现了...
I mean, Cindy showed up...
所以,马上,斯科特 你会异常兴奋
so, right away, Scott, you got to be pretty psyched, right?
我请你不是为了听你思索生活
Hey, buddy, I'm not paying you to hear your thoughts on life.
我是请你来唱歌
I'm paying you to sing.
我有麦克风,可你没有...
Well, I have a microphone, and you don't...
所以你会听到每句该死的话... 我就是要说
so you will listen to every damn word I have to say!
真可笑
You know, it's funny.
我们中有人永远也找不到真爱
Some of us will never, ever find true love.
比如,举个例吧...
Like, take, for instance...
我
me.
我肯定那个家伙也是
And I'm pretty sure that guy right there.
还有那位连鬓胡子的女士
And that lady with the sideburns.
还有九号桌上的所有人
And basically everybody at table nine.
Huh?
但最糟糕的是...
But the worst thing is...
我...
that me...
胖胖的...
fatty...
有连鬓胡子的女士...
sideburns lady...
还有九号桌那些形容古怪的人...
and the mutants over at table nine...
Aw.
将永远找不到改善处境的办法...
Will never, ever find a way to better the situation...
因为...
because...
很显然,我们根本没有什么能取悦...
apparently, we have absolutely nothing to offer...
异性
the opposite sex.
Mm-hmm.
你是世上最差劲的婚礼歌手,伙计
You are the worst wedding singer in the world, buddy!
先生,你要是再发火...
Sir, one more outburst...
我会用我的麦克风线勒死你
I will strangle you with my microphone wire.
听明白了吗?
You understand me?
我们来切这愚蠢的蛋糕吧...
Now let's cut the stupid cake...
因为那个胖子会受刺激...
because I know the fat guy's going to have a heart attack...
如果我们再不快吃的话
if we don't eat again soon.
与此同时,来首有点破坏情绪的歌
And while we do that, here's a little mood music for you.
# Whoo-hoo! #
辛迪和斯科特新婚燕尔
Cindy and Scott are newlyweds.
Whoopi-dee-do!
他爱着她...
# He loves her #
但她爱着这边这个男人...
# But she loves this guy right here #
而他爱的另有其人
# And he loves somebody else #
你无法获胜
# You just can't win #
所以就这样...
# And so it goes #
直到你死的那一天
# Until the day you die #
这玩意儿名叫爱情...
# This thing they call love #
会令你哭泣
# Is gonna make you cry #
我讨厌你
I hate you.
我有过伤心...
# I've had the blues #
愤怒和刺痛
# The reds and the pinks #
有件事是肯定的...
# One thing's for sure #
爱让人恶心?
Love stinks?
爱让人恶心
# Love stinks #
# Yeah, yeah #
爱让人恶心
Love stinks!
# Love stinks #
# Yeah, yeah #
爱让人恶心
Love stinks?
# Love stinks #
# Yeah, yeah #
爱让人恶心
Love stinks!
# Love stinks #
# Yeah, yeah #
是毒瘾,是堕落
Drug addict! Degenerate!
爱让人恶心
# Love stinks #
爱...让人恶心
# Love... Love stinks #
爱让人恶心
# Love stinks! #
Hey.
我想知道你怎么样
I was wondering what happened to you.
所有人都走了吗?
Did everybody leave?
差不多吧,除了几个警察...
Pretty much, except for a few cops...
还在询问那些服务生
that are still interviewing some witnesses.
OK.
我要离开这儿去地狱
I'm going to get the hell out of here.
这是你回来后第一次婚礼
OK, so it was your first wedding back...
出点偏差是正常的
Of course things are going to be a little shaky.
一点偏差?我憎恨婚礼
A little shaky? I hate weddings.
我憎恨新娘,憎恨新郎
I hate the bride. I hate the groom.
我希望他们痛苦,因为我就是那样
I want them to be miserable, because that's what I am.
不,你再好不过
No. You're the best.
哪方面好? 大家在吃上好的排骨时我在唱歌
At what? People eat prime rib, and I sing.
真是笑话,我不能再干这个了
I mean, it's a joke. I can't do this anymore.
格伦和我定好了日期...
Glenn and I set the date...
所以你得来我们的婚礼上表演
so you have to play our wedding.
恭喜
Congratulations.
我无法再干了,明白吗?
I... I just can't do it, all right?
两周后我有个订婚宴...
Well, I'm having an engagement party in two weeks...
我很希望你和山米能来
and I really want you and Sammy to come.
# Ohh ohh #
# Hold me now #
# Whoa, oh #
# Warm my heart #
# Stay with me #
很好,你来了
Oh, good, you're here.
罗比来了,我们走吧
Robbie's here! Let's move it!
孩子们都吃过了...
Now, the kids have been fed...
要是他们还想吃什么的话 冰箱里有冰淇淋...
but if they want snacks, there's ice pops in the freezer...
还有爆米花
or they can have microwave popcorn.
好的
Good.
你去参加订婚宴吗?
Are you going to the engagement party tomorrow night?
是的,很可能会去
Yeah, I'll probably go.
快点,安迪,别磨蹭了
Come on, Andy, move your ass!
等等,我在看"达拉斯"
Hang on, huh? I'm watching Dallas.
我想J.R恐怕死了,他中了枪
I think J.R. Might be dead or something. They shot him.
晚安
Good night.
-爱你 -爱你
- Love you. - Love you.
该做油炸圈饼了
Time to make the donuts.
-我做了油炸圈饼 -邓肯油炸圈饼
- I made the donuts. - Dunkin' Donuts.
你好
Hello.
罗比舅舅来了
Hey, Uncle Robbie's here.
嘿,呆瓜兄弟
Hey... ohh, the goofball brothers.
你真的处在神经崩溃之中吗?
Is it true that you're in the middle of a nervous breakdown?
不
No.
神经崩溃
Nervous breakdown, nervous breakdown.
-谁说的? -所有人
- Who said that? - Everybody's been saying that.
所有人?你才八岁,你只认识爸爸妈妈
Everybody? You're eight years old. You only know your parents.
你说的是什么?
What are you talking about?
你真的会在精神病院等死吗?
Is it true that you're gonna end up in a mental institution?
象布谷鸟的窝
Cuckoo's nest, cuckoo's nest.
才不是呢
No.
嘿,孩子们
Hey, hey, hey, kids. Shh.
记得我们说过什么吗?
Now, remember what we talked about?
好吧
All right.
去那边看电视吧
Go over there and watch some television.
可以和你聊一会吗?
Can I speak to you for a second, Rob?
所有人...
- Everybody... - Yeah.
我想过你的遭遇...
You know, I've been thinking about what happened to you...
但最好到此为止
and believe me, it's all for the best.
Yeah.
我知道你的恋爱经历和所有事情... 但那已经过去了
I mean, I know you were in love and everything, but that wears off.
我和你姐姐也曾疯狂过
You see, me and your sister, we used to be wild.
她很爱冒险...
She was very adventurous...
我们也曾对一些疯狂的事着迷 但现在已经不再冲动
and we got into some crazy shit, but now the thrill is gone.
我们单独在一起时通常就是睡觉
If we do get a second alone together, we usually go to sleep.
如果是特殊情况...
- Yeah? - I mean, if it's a special occasion...
她会为我表演脱衣舞
she might, uh, she might do this exotic dance for me.
什么?
What?
有时候还会...
And sometimes she might, uh...
玩弄我的乳头
you know, work with my nipples a little bit.
好了,够了,快滚吧 我会照看好孩子们的
All right, enough. Go out. I'll take care of the kids.
Yeah.
我不知道我说了些什么,但我肯定说了
I don't know what I just said, but I said something.
# Time #
女人很注重婚姻 如果你想和她们呆在一起
Women got a thing about marriage. I mean, if you want to stay with them...
你就得娶她们
eventually you're gonna have to marry them.
没什么大不了
That's the point that I'm at. No big deal.
她来了
There she is.
这就是最终征服了我的姑娘
The girl who finally beat me into submission.
没错 不到三个月就是八月五号了
That's right. August 5 is less than 3 months away.
我们有很多事要安排
We've got a lot of planning to do.
你觉得是不是这样比较好...
Um, do you think it would be better...
如果由你来安排一切的话?
if maybe you took over all the arrangements?
我希望一起安排
Well, I'd like to do it together.
是吗
Yeah.
可你喜欢做这些啊 我真的干不来这些事
But you like this stuff. It's really not my thing.
上帝不会允许我弄乱婚礼上的鲜花
I mean, God forbid I screw up the wedding flowers.
我怎么能一个人生活呢?
How could I live with myself?
他会非常浪费...
Hey, he's gonna be so wasted...
他不懂婚礼用花的事
he's not even gonna know flowers are at the wedding.
Oh, yeah. Up high.
我听说你们会在周五
Hey, Glenn, I hear you're gonna have your bachelor party...
举行你的单身聚会 那会令人满意吧?
Friday night before the wedding. Gonna be all right with that?
你也许会错过"迈阿密风云"
I mean, you might miss Miami Vice.
不,夏季会重播
Nope. Summer. Reruns.
我早安排好了
I'm all set.
太好了
Oh, great.
不错,房子真漂亮
All right, nice house.
我说过这家伙很有钱的
I told you this guy was loaded.
我知道,可是人来人往的
Yeah, I know. But in and out, though, man.
我不想呆太久
I don't want to be here very long.
等我去吊个马子
All right, let me just pick up a chick...
然后我们就走
and we'll get out of here.
你觉得这夹克怎么样?
What do you think of the jacket?
我会扔掉那手套,你看上去很怪异
I don't know, man. I would lose that glove. You look nuts.
那是茱莉娅
There's Julia.
我们去打个招呼
Let's go say hello.
嗨,你们好
Hi, you guys.
真高兴你们能来
I'm so glad you came.
杰森,这是罗比和山米...
Jason, this is Robbie and Sammy...
这是我的未婚夫格伦
and this is my fianc?Glenn.
-恭喜你,格伦 -谢谢
- Hey, congratulations, Glenn. - Thank you.
罗比-哈特
Robbie Hart. Oh, man...
我听说了你在婚礼上的遭遇
I heard what happened to you at your wedding.
那太残酷了,你肯定感觉很窝囊
That was so cold. You must have felt like shit.
不,感觉非常好
No. It felt really good.
谢谢你提及此事
Thanks for bringing it up, man.
我十岁时就父母双亡
You know, my parents died when I was ten.
想聊聊这事吗?
Would you like to talk about that?
我们干嘛要聊那些?
Why would we want to talk about that?
我不知道
I don't know.
有人需要来一杯
Hey, oh, somebody needs a drink.
实际上我并不是酒鬼
Actually, I'm not a big drinker.
我是,来杯"阿拉巴马监狱"怎么样?
Well, I am. How about an Alabama slammer?
听上去象是行动计划
Sounds like a plan.
酒吧见,我先去撒泡尿
Meet me at the bar. I gotta piss first.
对,喝上几杯然后开车回家
Hey, yeah, have a few drinks and, you know, drive home.
茱莉娅,谢谢你邀请我们
Hey, Julia, thanks for inviting us.
我很高兴你们能来
I'm just glad you guys came.
我们共事这么久了...
I mean, we get to hang out at work so much...
但"我们一直在忙"总不是理由
but we don't get to talk 'cause we're always so busy.
我们该找时间谈谈,你觉得呢?
Well, we should make time to talk, don't you think?
知道吗?这家伙第一次看到你时...
You know what? The first time this guy saw you...
就跟我说他说要泡你
he told me he was gonna hit on you.
-是吗? -没这事
- Really? - That's not true.
不,有的,你跟我说她有麻烦了
Yeah, it is. You told me she was in trouble.
她就要遇上麻烦而她一点都不知道
She was gonna get it, and she didn't even know it.
他在说笑,我从没那样说过
He's teasing. I would never say that.
你说你要去找她麻烦的
What? You said you were gonna give it to her.
具体说是找我什么麻烦呢?
- Give me what, exactly? - Yeah.
你是个笨蛋
You're a jerk.
你什么意思? 你并不知道她已经订婚啊
What do you mean? You didn't know she was engaged.
所以你现在不找我麻烦了?
So now you're not gonna give it to me?
太有趣了
Very funny.
向你兄弟提托问好
Say hi to your brother Tito.
那么你怎么样?
So, how are you doing?
我好些了,说不清
I'm doing better. I don't know.
你和格伦的婚事安排得怎么样了?
How are you and Glenn doing with the wedding plans?
Uh...
格伦并没有太...
Glenn isn't really...
他现在真的很忙
He's... He's very busy right now.
他在华尔街工作
You know, he works on Wall Street...
你知道那里现在是什么情况
and you know how that is nowadays.
华尔街--股票和现金?
Wall Street, stocks and stuff?
实际上他从事的是债券行业
Yeah. Actually, he's in bonds.
他几乎没有时间睡觉, 假设独自安排婚礼的话...
And he barely has time to sleep, let alone plan a wedding...
所以差不多是我一个人安排的
so I'm kind of doing this on my own.
我为了花饰的事去过马歇尔的店
But I went to Marshall's for the floral centerpieces.
马歇尔?你应该去托尼的店
You went to Marshall's? Man, you should go to Tony's.
他那儿比较便宜,而且有不错的选择
They're cheaper, you know, and they've got a great selection.
好的,谢谢你的建议
All right. Well, thank you for the tip.
你不再主持婚礼真是可惜
You know, it's a shame you won't be doing weddings anymore.
我们不能继续共事了
We won't get to hang out as much.
我们还会是同事
Nah, we'll get to hang out.
婚礼之外还有...
There's other things to do at the reception hall...
其他事情可做不是吗?
besides weddings, right?
# Oy, oy, bar mitzvah #
# Mazel tov #
# Ya ya ya #
# L'chaim! #
让我们继续这欢快的舞蹈吧
OK, let's keep the fun rolling. Take it away, George.
这是谁呢?
- Yeah! - Who's this?
你真的想伤害我吗...
# Do you really want to hurt me? #
你看起来有点难过
You seem kind of sad.
你为什么不去跳舞呢?
Why don't you get out there and dance, buddy?
我邀请过那边那个女孩
I asked that girl over there.
可她拒绝了我
She turned me down.
她说她不和失败者跳舞
She said she didn't dance with losers.
老天,真是伤人
Oh, man. That hurts.
但你为什么不找个...
But, you know, why would you want to dance with somebody...
愿意和你跳舞的人呢? 你说是吧?
who doesn't want to dance with you? Right?
听着,别担心
Listen, don't worry.
总有一天你会遇见一个善待你的女孩
You're gonna meet a girl who treats you right someday.
我向你保证
I promise you. OK, buddy?
你们怎么样?都好吗?
How you guys doing? All right?
我要向你们介绍一位朋友...
Fellas, I want you to meet a friend of mine...
名叫茱莉娅-沙利文
by the name of Julia Sullivan.
你能过来一下吗?
Hiya, Julia. Could you come out here for a second?
-大家向茱莉娅问个好 -你好
- Say hi to Julia, everybody. - Hello.
现在,有谁愿意出来 和这位漂亮的女士跳舞?
Now, who of you out there would like to dance with this fine-Iooking woman?
我,我!
- Oh, me! Me! - Yeah!
我想的可不只是和她跳舞
I'd like to do more than dance with her.
哇,茱莉娅
Wow, Julia.
我想要你自己挑选...
Sounds to me like you got your pick...
在座的任何一个男性...
of any man in this room to dance with...
所以我会给你时间...
so I want you to take your time...
在今晚来的这些小男士当中选出...
and find amongst all these young studs here tonight...
最酷,最棒的人来
the coolest, most un-Iosery guy in the bunch.
好的
OK.
选我
Pick me, pick me.
Feel my love, baby.
请选我
Please pick me. Please, Julia.
Oh, please.
可以和我跳舞吗?
May I have this dance?
Ahhh!
好了,伙计,开心点
OK, pal, have fun.
我只能把爱交给你...
# I can only give you love #
直到永远...
# That lasts forever #
每次你来电话
# And a promise to be near #
都象是一个承诺
# Each time you call #
我只有一颗心...
# And the only heart I own #
给你,独一无二的你...
# For you and you alone #
这就是全部
# That's all #
Ohh!
这就是全部
# That's all #
Uh-oh.
我只有这双手臂...
# All I have are these arms #
来拥抱你
# To enfold you #
继续跳
Just go with it.
爱的时刻将会永存
# And a love time can never destroy #
接下去,乔治
Take it, George.
过来
Come here, big red.
如果你想知道我的请求...
# If you're wondering what I'm asking #
作为回答,亲爱的...
# In return, dear #
你会高兴地知道...
# You'll be glad to know #
我的要求不高
# That my demands are small #
说我是你的最爱...
# Say it's me that you'll adore #
从现在直到永远
# For now and ever more #
这就是全部
# That's all #
献给女士们的新国王
To the new lord of the ladies!
你是个可爱的舞伴
You're a lovely dancer.
-你会告诉格伦吗? -关于什么?
- Are you gonna tell Glenn? - About what?
你和那孩子以及他捏你屁股的事啊
About you and that kid, and him squeezing your tush.
以十三岁来说他的手算是非常有力了
Well, he did have very strong hands for a thirteen-year-old.
我知道
I could see that.
另外...
Hey, listen, by the way...
谢谢你向我推荐托尼的花店
thank you for recommending Tony the florist.
他的花很漂亮,而且要价不高
Not only were his flowers beautiful, but he didn't overcharge me.
不错啊
Good. I'm glad.
镇上新来的女孩... 肯定能在各方面得到这种帮助
And a new girl in town could certainly use that kind of help on everything.
你有霍莉和你妈妈帮你不是吗?
You got Holly and your mother, right?
我妈妈住在五十英里以外...
Well, my mother lives fifty miles away...
而霍莉又不熟悉这一行...
and Holly's not into that kind of thing...
所以只剩下一个人选
so that really only leaves one person.
乔治?
George?
哦,不
No.
我愿意帮你,但... 你知道的,我不能...
I would, but, you know, I just... I can't.
我明白
I understand.
我只是不知道该怎么做
I just don't know how to go about this.
我担心自己 会花五百块买个吃了一半的结婚蛋糕
I'm afraid I'm gonna pay $500 for a half-eaten wedding cake.
我确实得多揽一些演出机会
I really gotta concentrate on getting some more gigs.
这个镇上只有四家犹太人
I mean, there's only four Jewish families in this town.
好吧
Oh, all right.
Yay.
# It's all I can do... #
我从没收过这么低的费用
I have never done it for that cheap.
我知道你给过埃里克-拉蒙索夫这个价
Hey, I know for a fact you gave Eric Lamensoft that price.
没有
I did not.
嘿嘿,看着我
Faye, look at me.
看着我的眼睛,我在这边
Look me in the eyes. I'm right here, Faye.
不要看别处
Don't look away.
你有没给过他这个价?
Tell me, did you give him that price or not?
呃
Mmm.
好吧,只有那一次,你赢了
OK. Just that one time. OK, so you got me.
不介意我说几句吧?
Hey, you know, can I say something?
我接待过许多人, 但你俩看起来真的很幸福
I deal with a lot of people, but you two look truly happy.
你们会幸福的,我知道,相信我
You're gonna make it. I know. Believe me.
你怎么知道呢?
How do you know?
你只要看到一对夫妇...
Well, you know, you can just look at a couple...
就能作出准确的判断...
and you can tell right away...
他们将会永远在一起
that they're gonna stay together forever.
就象唐纳德和伊凡娜...
Like, uh, Donald and Ivana...
伍迪和米娅...
and Woody and Mia...
伯特和朗莉
and Burt and Loni.
我们可不会结婚
Oh, well, we're not getting married.
是啊,实际上我们是兄妹
That's right. Actually, we're brother and sister.
正是这样
Oh, so that's it.
我可以感觉到那份亲密感
Oh, 'cause I could sense a closeness.
奇怪的是...
You know, the weird thing is...
从小到大 我们相处得并不好
when we were growing up, we didn't get along...
因为我总是对她这样
'cause I used to do this to her a lot.
Ow!
Aah!
我们得走了,来吧,妹妹
We're gonna go now. Come here, sis.
你这个混蛋
Hey, your ass is grass.
回家后我要告诉妈妈
I'm telling Mom when we get home.
Whoo!
这是女士之夜...
# Yes, it's ladies' night #
而且感觉不错
# And the feeling's right #
这是女士之夜
# Oh, yes, it's ladies' night #
哦,多美的夜晚
# Oh, what a, oh, what a night #
没错,这是女士之夜...
# Yes, it's ladies' night #
而且感觉不错
# And the feeling's right #
我以前从没以观众的身份看过这些
Man, I've never seen it from this perspective before.
我看起来象这样吗?
Is this what I look like?
不,你比他棒多了
No, no. No, you're much better than him.
他很可笑
He's ridiculous.
一个...
# One, hoo #
# Hoo, hoo, hoo #
浪漫的女士...
# Romantic lady #
单身的宝贝...
# Single baby #
老练的女人...
# Mmm, sophisticated mama #
来吧,你这迪斯科女郎
# Come on, you disco lady #
给我一根红绳,女士
# Send me a line, mama #
这是女士之夜
# Yes, it's ladies' night #
哦,多美的夜晚
# Oh, what a night #
# Chaka Khan #
谢谢大家,我是吉米-摩尔...
Thank you. This is Jimmy Moore...
格言是"我的胯间可没有零食"
saying that ain't no sock in my crotch.
大家休息一下
OK, take four, everybody.
吉米,表演真精彩,谢谢你
Jimmy, that was really good, man. Thank you.
-不,要谢谢你 -谢什么?
- Hey, no. Thank you. - For what?
你辞职啊
For quitting.
也许...该感谢琳达?
Or... should I thank Linda?
我的生意好了三倍
My business has tripled.
你让我想到可以去找个D.J...
Well, you've just inspired me to hire a DJ.
谢谢你
So thank you.
Oh.
祝你好运能找到个...
Well, good luck finding a DJ...
会象这样扭动的D.J
who can move and shake like this.
你怎么会成为婚礼歌手的?
How did you become a wedding singer?
我觉得我能靠这个挣点钱...
I think I got into it to make some money...
在我的音乐事业成功之前
until my music career took off.
你想成为一名摇滚歌星吗?
And you want to be a rock star?
我希望自己可以创作,明白吗?
I kind of just wanted to be a songwriter, you know?
写一首歌最困难的是...
I think that's the hardest thing, to write a song.
当人们听到这样一首歌时...
A song that... you know, when people hear it...
他们说 "哦,我明白那家伙写这首歌时的感受"
they go, "Ohh, I know what that guy was feeling when he wrote that."
你最近有没有写?
Have you written anything lately?
是的,我有
Yeah, I guess.
可以为我表演一下吗?
Will you play it for me?
你不会想听的,写得并不好
You don't want to hear it. It's not good.
我相信会很好
No, I'm sure it is.
我和琳达在一起时写了一半...
It's just... I wrote half of it when I was with Linda...
我们分手后写了另一半...
and I wrote the other half after we broke up...
所以有点不协调,知道吗
so it's a little uneven, you know?
我不介意
I don't mind.
我只想听听
I'd like to hear it.
那好吧
Yeah, all right.
Yay.
我要警告你,当我写这歌的时候...
OK, I just want to warn you that, uh, when I wrote this song...
我听了很多"The Curt"的歌, 所以...
I was listening to The Cure a lot, so...
明白
OK.
开始了
Here we go.
你不知道...
# You don't know #
我多么
# How much #
需要你
# I need you #
你在我身边时...
# While you're near me #
我不会感到忧伤
# I don't feel blue #
当我们接吻时...
# And when we kiss #
我知道你也需要我
# I know you need me, too #
我不敢相信自己找到了一份爱...
# I can't believe I found a love #
那样纯净和真实...
# That's so pure and true #
但那全是胡说八道
# But it all was bullshit #
是一个见鬼的玩笑...
# It was a goddamn joke #
当我想到你时,琳达...
# And when I think of you, Linda #
我希望你窒息
# I hope you fuckin' choke #
但愿你感到高兴...
# I hope you're glad #
为你对我所做的事
# With what you've done to me #
我躺在床上...
# I lay in bed #
一整天...
# All day long #
忧伤难过
# Feeling melancholy #
你丢下了我...
# You left me here #
独自一个...
# All alone #
泪流不止
# Tears running constantly #
哦,求求谁杀了我吧
# Oh, somebody kill me, please #
求求谁杀了我吧
# Somebody kill me, please #
我跪地请求
# I'm on my knees #
真的真的求求你
# Pretty, pretty please #
杀了我
# Kill me #
我想死
# I want to die #
冲我的脑袋来一枪
# Put a bullet in my head #
我宁愿这样
I liked it.
他疯了...
He's losing his mind.
而我该捡便宜了
And I'm reaping all the benefits.
谢谢你请我吃冰淇淋, 它总能让我精神振奋
Thank you for the ice cream. It always cheers me up some.
用不着客气
It's my pleasure.
来这里我感觉很怪
I feel weird being in this place.
我们经常来这
You know, Linda and I used to come here all the time.
我们总是要巧克力混合饮料
We used to get chocolate shakes.
介意我问问琳达的事吗?
May I ask what happened with Linda?
我想是因为她不适合我吧
She wasn't the right one, I guess.
当你们在一起时
Did you have any idea she wasn't the right one...
你有没有想过她不适合你?
when you were together?
应该有的
I should have.
记得有次我们去了大峡谷
Uhh, I remember we went to the Grand Canyon one time.
是乘飞机去的,之前我从没去过...
We were flying there, and I'd never been there before...
但琳达去过...
and Linda had...
你可能以为她会让我坐靠窗的位置...
so you would think that she would give me the window seat...
但她没有
but she didn't.
那没什么大不了,不是吗?
Not that that's a big deal, you know?
但有很多诸如此类的小事
But just... there were a lot of little things like that.
-我知道这听起来很蠢 -一点也不
- I know that sounds stupid. - Not at all.
我觉得小事情也很重要
I think it's the little things that count.
你怎么知道格伦是理想的对象呢?
How did you know that Glenn was the right one?
理想的对象
The right one.
我总是想象理想的对象...
I always just envisioned the right one...
是某个我能看着自己和他一起变老的人
being someone I could see myself growing old with.
Yeah.
而格伦会变成一个很帅的老头...
And Glenn will be a really good-looking older man...
就象布莱克-卡林顿
like Blake Carrington.
我也许会变得象巴蒂-哈克特
I'm gonna probably look like Buddy Hackett.
哈哈
Ha ha ha ha!
# What I want, you've got #
# But it might be hard to handle #
# Like the flame that burns the candle #
# The candle feeds the flame #
# Yeah, yeah, what I got, full stock #
# Of thoughts and dreams that scatter #
# And you pull them all together #
# And how I can't explain #
# Oh, yeah #
# Well, well, you #
# You make my dreams come true #
# Well, well, well, you #
# Oh, yeah #
# You make my dreams come true #
# On a night when bad dreams #
# Become a Screamer #
# When they're messin' with a dreamer #
# I can laugh it in the face #
# Twist and shout my way out #
# And wrap yourself around me #
我当然会雇他 他是你最好的朋友
Of course I'm gonna hire him. Not only is he your best friend...
而且是镇上唯一的豪华轿车司机
but he's the only limo driver in town.
是的,我喜欢和他逗乐
Yeah. I just like having fun with him.
OK.
哇,看看他的样子
Wow. Look at him go.
# Listen to this #
最好快点,老兄
Better move it, man.
你会来不及了
You're not gonna make it.
你撞倒了两个路障, 那些有可能是人呢
You hit two cones. Those could have been people.
有可能是来参加婚礼的宾客
Those could have been guests at her wedding.
只是路障罢了
They were cones.
# Every day, every day, every day #
# Every day I write the book #
# Chapter one #
今天很有意思是不是?
That was fun today. Wasn't that fun?
很有趣
That was fun.
我得到这份工作了是吧?
I got the job, right?
是的,你做到了 八月五号,还有一个礼拜
Yeah, you did. It's August 5, a week from today.
有人把夹克落在后面了
Cool. Hey, someone left a jacket in the back.
是茱莉娅的夹克
That's Julia's jacket.
记得吗?她在诺克森街脱下来的
Remember? She took it off on Noxon street.
她说不是穿夹克的天气了
She said it's not jacket weather anymore.
哦噢
Uh-oh.
怎么了?
What?
-你喜欢她 -没,我没有
- You like her. - No, I don't.
你当然有, 她很可爱,还有个漂亮的屁股
Of course you do. She's a cool chick with a hot ass.
你再提她的屁股我就扭断你的脖子
How's this? You talk about her ass again, I'll break your neck.
不过她跟我说过她喜欢你
Anyway, she told me she likes you.
真的吗?她那样说过?
Really? She said that?
没有
No.
想想吧
I mean, think about it.
那将是你们作为夫妻的第一个吻
It's gonna be your first kiss as a married couple.
张开你的嘴是完全可以接受的
It's perfectly acceptable to open your mouth.
我可不想在教堂那样做...
I just would not want to do that in a church...
当着上帝和所有亲友的面
in front of God and all of our relatives.
看到我这样会让他们恶心的...
I mean, it would gross them out to see me like...
没人能玩出来
No one will ever solve that.
Hi.
你把夹克落在车上了
You forgot your jacket in the limo.
谢谢你把它送过来,你真是太好了
Thank you for bringing it back. That's so nice of you.
是的,没错
Yeah, it was.
回头见好吗?玩得开心点
OK, I'll see you later, all right? Have fun today.
嘿,等等
Hey, wait. Wait a second.
也许...
Maybe...
他能帮帮我们
maybe he can help us.
你是行家
You're the expert on this.
我们刚才在讨论婚礼接吻的事
We were just having a debate about wedding kisses.
我觉得张开嘴接吻没问题
I say that it's OK for it to be an open-mouth kiss.
但我觉得在大家穿着
And I say that it's the type of occasion...
很庄重的场合 那样做并不合适
where people dress up, so it's not appropriate.
-我明白 -你想怎么做?
- I see. - What do you want to do?
轻轻的,闭着嘴,就这样完事?
I mean, thin, tight mouth, and it's over?
不,轻轻的,略微张开嘴
No. Thin, partially opened...
不用舌头,就这样
no tongues, over.
不用舌头?拜托
No tongue? Please.
总得有一点点接触
God, there has got to be a little tongue.
也许就一点点
Well, maybe a little tongue.
不是激烈的舌吻,是教堂式的舌吻
Not porno tongue. Church tongue.
教堂式舌吻,我喜欢这个
Church tongue. I like that.
教堂式舌吻?怎么讲?
Church tongue? What... What is that?
我不知道该怎么说
I don't know how to describe it.
那就做给我看看
Well, show me.
不是和我
Not on me.
和他怎么样?
Hey, how about on him?
你不会介意对吧?
You don't mind, do you?
-我... -来吧,站好别动
- I, uh... - Come on, just hold still.
茱莉娅,来吧
Julia, go ahead.
来呀,我们都是成年人
Come on. We're all adults here.
我想要看看...
I'm gonna have to see it...
好长点见识
if I'm gonna make an educated decision.
好吧,如果只是出于教育目的的话
Well, if it's for educational purposes.
这就对了
Good. OK.
你准备好了吗?
All right, you ready?
我现在宣布你们结为夫妻
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
你可以吻新娘了
You may kiss the bride.
Wow.
这...
That...
真是...太棒了
was... great.
茱莉娅,你在婚礼上就这么做好了
Julia, you should do that at the wedding.
我是来送夹克给她的
I gave her the jacket.
嘿,茱莉娅,嘿,霍莉
Hey, Jules. Hey, Holly.
嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
Hey.
我吻了她,但那并不意味着什么
I kissed her, but it didn't mean anything.
我只是来送夹克给她
I just brought her the jacket.
吻谁?
Kissed who?
哦,我
Oh, me.
有谁没吻过呢?
Who hasn't?
我有东西给你,这个叫CD机
I got you something. It's called a CD player.
花了我七百块呢...
It cost me, like, 700 bucks...
但是音效很不错
but the sound quality is outstanding.
你想放张唱片吗?
You want to play a record?
茱莉娅,这不是用来放唱片的,是放CD的
No, Jules, it doesn't play records. It plays CDs.
这是CD机
It's a CD player.
我上楼去把它放好
I'll be upstairs hooking it up.
哦,我的天,罗比真是可爱得让人吃惊
Julia! Oh, my God, Robbie is so amazingly cute.
我想我应该和他约会
I think I should go out with him.
对,为什么不呢?
Yeah, I mean, why not?
你是单身,他也是单身,顺理成章
You're single, and he's single. It makes sense.
如果你不愿意的话我就不这么做
Well, hey, if you don't want me to, I won't do it.
我为什么会不愿意?
Why would I not want you to?
很好,那我就去和他约会啦
Good, then I'm going out with him.
和谁约会?
Who you going out with?
罗比
Robbie.
很好,那家伙是该有性交往了
Good. That guy needs to get laid.
不见得吧 因为他和我约会
Excuse me. Just because he's going out with me...
并不意味着他会提出性要求
doesn't mean he's gonna get laid.
好吧,也许他会
All right, he probably will.
你觉得他会和我约会吗?
I mean, do you think he'll go out with me?
茱莉娅和他很熟
Yeah. Jules is chums with him.
让她来安排不是正好吗?
She'll fix it up, won't you, Jules?
想想看会多有意思
Hey, you guys, you know what would be fun?
我们可以来个四人约会
Let's... Let's all go on a double date.
好的
OK.
你确定你知道自己在做什么吗？
You sure you know what you're doing up there?
别担心 你得保持体形...
Don't worry. You've got to stay in shape...
其他男人就会看你
so other men will look at you.
这样你丈夫会发现你魅力犹存
That way your husband knows you're still attractive.
是吗，只是别把哑铃掉脑袋上了
Yeah, well, just don't drop a dumbbell on your head.
Mm. Ha ha.
那么，你还没有新的约会对象，是吗？
So, you still haven't been dating anyone new, have you?
是的，还没有
No, not yet.
是自信心的问题吗？
Is it your confidence?
你对你的鸡巴感到不安吗？
Are you nervous about your penis?
嗯？什么？
Huh? What?
当你给新的女孩子展示鸡巴的时候， 是否会感到不安？
Well, are you nervous about showing a new girl your penis?
你给琳达展示鸡巴的时候也许很自在...
You were comfortable showing it to Linda...
但你现在不得不展示给另外的人看
but now you might have to show your penis to someone new.
你怎么回事？ 别...别谈这话题
What's the matter with you? Don't... Don't talk about that.
你知道，当你还是个孩子的时候
You know, I was at your bris when you were a baby...
我见过它
and I saw it.
虽不大，但也不怎么小
It wasn't huge, but it had some size.
所以没必要担心它
So don't worry about it.
我并不担心 换个话题，快点
I'm not worried about it. Next subject, quick.
- 形状还不错 - 你怎么回事？
- It had good shape. - What's the matter with you?
如果能再切掉点多余的皮肤的话...
And when they cut the extra skin off...
鸡巴就会显得很干净
the penis itself was very clean.
真是妙极了，老天
Well, that's great. Jeez.
露茜，当我准备好的时候， 我会去找女孩子约会的
I'm going to ask a girl out when I'm ready, Rosie.
哦，那么，在这之前让我帮你练习一下
Oh, well, let me help you practice until you are.
现在，我是个年轻姑娘，你是罗比
Now, I'll be a young girl, and you be Robbie.
来，约我出去
So, ask me out.
我不想这样做
I don't want to do this.
你好，先生
Hello, sir.
你好
Hello.
你有什么要问我的吗？
Is there something you want to ask me?
是的. 你愿意和我一起吃个晚餐吗？
OK. Would you like to go to dinner with me sometime?
不行. 你鸡巴太小了
No. Your penis is too small.
哈哈哈！ 开玩笑的，开玩笑的.
Ha ha ha! I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
我刚才所说了，它也不怎么小
As I said, it had some size.
好的
OK.
哦，罗比
Oh, Robbie.
你会知道你何时会遇到合适的女孩的...
You'll know when you meet the right girl...
因为这不是你对她的感觉怎么样...
because it's not how you feel about her...
而是她使你感觉到自己怎么样
it's how she makes you feel about yourself.
似乎寓意深长
That makes a lot of sense.
虽然其它的听上去荒唐一点...
All that other stuff was ridiculous...
但这句倒是寓意深长
but that made a lot of sense.
啊，看看谁来了 可爱的天使
Ah, well, look who we have here. The precious angel.
嗨，露茜
Hi, Rosie.
课程进行得怎么样？
How are the lessons going?
我想我开始掌握到窍门了
Well, I think I'm starting to get the hang of it.
是的，她唱歌时受惊吓的人越来越少了
Yeah, she's starting to scare less and less people when she sings.
哦，罗比，你真是爱开玩笑
Oh, Robbie, you're so funny.
你俩谈吧
You two talk.
我想再做一些推举锻炼
I'm going to do some more military presses.
一切都好吗？
OK. Everything all right?
是的. 实际上，呃...
Yeah. Actually, um...
我来是想问你件事
I came by to ask you something though.
是吗？什么事情？
Yeah? What's up?
呃...
Um...
你愿意和霍莉约会吗？
Would you like to go out on a date with Holly?
哦，是吗？你想让我和霍莉约会？
Oh, yeah? You want me to go out on a date with Holly?
是的
Yeah.
那将会是个双重约会 格伦和我也准备去
It'll be a double date. Glenn and I are going to go, too.
哦，是吗？
Oh, yeah?
哦，是的，霍莉很不错
Oh, yeah, Holly's nice.
是的
Yeah.
她单身，你也单身
And she's single, and you're single.
是的
Yeah.
去吧，会很有意思的
Come on, it'll be fun.
是的，听上去很有趣
Yeah, that sounds like fun.
# How does it feel #
# To treat me like you do? #
# You place your hands upon me #
# And told me who you are #
# I thought I was mistaken #
# I thought I heard your words... #
罗比，你今晚看起来真可爱
Robbie, you look so cute tonight.
谢谢
Thank you.
我喜欢这些橡皮手镯, 你看上去就象玛当娜
I like these rubber bracelets. You look like Madonna.
对,正是这样
Yeah, well, that's the idea.
给你
Here you go.
那么,罗比,你的生意怎么样?
So, Robbie, how's your business going?
实际上我正在做一个游戏项目
I'm actually working on a game plan right now.
你应该留意一下债券市场
You should look into the bond market.
钱都在那里
That's where the money is.
格伦在经营垃圾债券
Glenn's in junk bonds.
不,茱莉娅,那是高回报的债券
No, Jules, it's high-yield bonds.
我跟谁说过你是做廉价招待的吗?
Do I tell people you're in junk waitressing?
Uhh.
我小时候祖母给过我一份储蓄债券
My grandmother gave me a savings bond when I was a kid.
93年我得到了二十五块,那很不错
I get $25 in 1993, so that'll be good.
Whoa.
我们看起来十足象对夫妻
So we totally look like a couple.
你们觉得我们是不是很好的一对?
I mean, don't you think we look great together?
Yeah.
大卫-鲍威的歌,他是最棒的
David Bowie playing. He's the best.
我猜他九月会来这里
You know, I think he's coming to town in September.
我喜欢大卫-鲍威
I love David Bowie.
当我兴奋的时候...
# When I get excited #
我的中国小姑娘...
# My little China girl #
她说
# She says #
"哦,宝贝,闭上你的嘴"
# Oh, baby, just you shut your mouth #
闭上你的嘴,没错
Shut your mouth. All right.
我们都熟悉歌词
We all know the words.
老天,我爱大卫-鲍威,他太性感了
God, I love David Bowie. He is so sexy.
你觉得做油炸饼圈广告的家伙也很性感
You think the "time to make the donuts" guy is sexy.
那家伙是很有趣
That guy is funny.
知道我还觉得谁性感吗?
You know who else I think is sexy?
罗比-哈特
Robbie Hart.
味道很好,非常感谢
Mmm, that's good. Thank you very much.
我得去洗手间
I gotta go to the bathroom.
失陪一会,我们很快就回来
Excuse us, guys. We'll be right back. It's OK.
她只要吐掉感觉就会好些
She'll feel better once she yaks.
但愿如此
I hope so.
那么...
So, uh...
礼拜天是大日子,对吧?
Sunday's the big day, huh?
我还不知道你姓什么呢
I don't even know your last name.
古力亚
It's Gulia.
Gulia.
茱莉娅的姓氏将会是古力亚
Julia's last name's gonna be Gulia.
茱莉娅-古力亚,真有趣
Julia Gulia. That's funny.
为什么有趣?
Why is that funny?
我说不好
I don't know.
# Shhhhh #
# She says #
你兴奋吗?
Are you excited?
是的,这是她应得的,她跟了我四年了
Yeah. She's paid her dues, been with me four years.
我用结婚来回报她
I owe it to her to get married.
You had the Long Island iced tea.
另外,要知道,也许 你也想要结婚
Plus, you know, you probably, uh, you want to get married.
我不想分手
I don't want to break up.
再说,她在我有钱之前就跟了我...
Plus she was with me before I made my money...
所以我知道我可以信赖她
so I know I can trust her.
那屁股真诱人不是吗?
That is a luscious ass right there, isn't it?
我的天
Mmm. My God.
那是一流的,顶级美味
That's grade-A, top-choice meat.
真想过去咬上一口
Like to bite right through that thing. Rrr.
嚼上一嚼
You know, chew on it.
可我们不可能再泡到那种小妞
But we can't get chicks like that anymore, you know?
我们太老了
We're too old.
那是说你,我可不老
Speak for yourself. I'm not too old.
我还能泡到那样的小妞
I can still get chicks like that.
尽管没那么惹火,对吧?
Not that hot, though, right?
更惹火的我都泡过
I've gotten hotter.
十年前
Ten years ago.
十天前就试过
Try ten days ago.
真的吗?
Really?
象那样的辣妹?
As hot as that?
更辣更年轻
Hotter... and younger.
你怎么做到的,伙计?
How do you do it, man?
你怎么能做到不被逮住的呢?
I mean, how do you do it without getting caught?
茱莉娅的精力全放在婚礼上了
Julia is totally preoccupied with the wedding.
她不会知道这些
I mean, she doesn't know what's going on.
哦,老兄
Oh, man.
可你知道讨厌的是什么吗?
You know what sucks, though?
一旦结婚,狂欢就结束了,是吧?
Once you get married, the party's over, right?
I mean...
我是在大都市工作,伙计
I work in the city, man.
而且工作时间很长
And I work long hours.
哦,原来如此
Yeah, that's something.
茱莉娅感觉不太舒服
Hey, guys. Julia's feeling a little under the weather.
我早说了她会吐吧
Told you she was gonna yak.
对,你说过
Yeah, you called it.
你们干嘛不去取车到门口等我们呢?
Why don't you go get your car and meet us out front?
哦,老天,我忘了我的钱包
Oh, God. I forgot my purse.
帮帮忙把她送到格伦车上去
Here. Do me a favor and put her in the car with Glenn, OK?
-没问题 -没事了,没事了
- OK, no problem. - It's OK. It's OK.
我吐了
I puked.
别在意
OK. Don't worry.
我吐到头发上了
I vomited in my hair.
没关系
All right.
我的头发很难闻吧?
Does my hair smell bad?
# Love my way... #
不,实际上很好闻
No, it smells good, actually.
感觉好些了是吧?
Just feel better, all right?
# I fall low #
# When my mind goes there #
嗨,格伦
Hi, Glenn.
OK.
别吐在车上,行吗?
Don't puke in the car, all right?
那会臭上一个星期
It'll stink for a week.
-再见,罗比 -再见,茱莉娅
- Bye, Robbie. - Bye, Julia.
# I fall low #
# When my mind goes #
# Love my way #
# It's a new... #
你觉得格伦怎么样?
Holly, what do you think of this Glenn guy?
你认为他值得信赖吗?
Do you think he's trustworthy?
是的,他很不错
- Yeah, he better be. - Yeah.
谁在乎格伦呢?
Who cares about Glenn?
你知道我一直在想什么吗?
You know what I keep thinking about?
什么?
What?
那天那个温柔的吻
That soft kiss from the other day.
看起来非常美妙
It looked... really nice.
哦,是的
Oh, yeah.
感觉好不好?
Did it feel good?
我不知道.我不...
I don't know. I don't...
不记得了
I don't remember.
要我唤起你的记忆吗?
Could I refresh your memory?
Mmm.
真棒
Yummy.
你该知道茱莉娅今晚会留在格伦家
So, you know Julia's staying at Glenn's tonight.
Oh.
听我说,罗比...
Look, Robbie, I know...
我知道你害羞...
that you're shy, and...
也知道你受过伤害...
I know that you've been hurt, so...
所以我想让你放松下来
I'm gonna make this really easy on you.
如果你上来的话...
If you come upstairs...
我们可以做爱
you're gonna get laid.
哇哦
Wow.
以前从没有人这么跟我说过
Nobody's ever said that to me before. Um...
我只是...我得告诉你...
I just... I'm telling you...
我现在有点心烦意乱
my head's kind of a mess right now.
茱莉娅会在格伦家过夜是吗?
Julia's staying at Glenn's tonight, huh?
是的
Yeah.
她经常在那过夜吗?
Does she stay over there a lot?
是啊
Yeah.
真的吗?
Really?
哦,上帝啊
Oh, my God.
怎么了?
What?
真不敢相信我以前从没注意到
I can't believe I never noticed it before.
什么?
What?
你爱上茱莉娅了
You've got a thing for Julia.
哦,不,我没有
Oh, no, I don't. I don't. I...
我觉得她是个很好的女孩... 但她就要嫁给那个傻瓜了
I think she's a very nice girl, but she's marrying that jerk-off.
你知道她为什么要嫁给他吗?
Hey. I mean, you know why she's marrying him, don't you?
为了钱?
The money thing?
证券?漂亮的房子?
Security? A nice house?
我想那对有些人来说是很重要
Uh, I guess that's important to some people.
不,这些...
No, it's...
不是对某些人重要,罗比
it's not important to some people, Robbie.
是对所有人都重要
It's important to all people.
是吗?那我猜我有大麻烦了
Really? Well, then I guess I'm in big trouble.
早啊,宝贝
Hey. Morning, sunshine.
我头疼得厉害 真的很疼
Oh, I have a bad headache, a really bad headache.
要我替你做早餐吗?
Can I cook you some breakfast?
# I was walkin'... #
昨晚那瓶朗姆酒怎么样?
How was your bottle of rum last night?
# Just a-Iookin' for someone to meet... #
我没有吐在你身上吧?
I didn't vomit on you, did I?
吐了一点在我的鞋上
A little on my shoe, but...
不过我穿的是你的鞋
luckily, I was wearing your shoes.
那就好
Good.
# I was hopin', hopin'... #
那么,昨晚你和罗比进展怎么样?
So, did anything happen with Robbie last night?
# Wonderin' #
# If you'd stay for the night... #
吻了一下
A kiss.
# I don't wanna be Ionely... #
你吻他还是他吻你?
Who kissed who? Did you kiss him, or did he kiss you?
-我吻他 -然后呢?
- I kissed him. - And then what?
就没了
Nothing.
# Do you believe in love... #
可他肯定不怎么看好格伦
I'll tell you, he sure doesn't think much of Glenn, though.
是吗?他怎么说?
Really? What did he say?
说格伦是个傻瓜
That Glenn's a jerk-off.
# You're makin' me believe it, too... #
他为什么那样说?
Why would he say that?
谁知道呢?也许他是嫉妒吧
I mean, who knows? Maybe... maybe he was jealous.
别担心, 我跟他说了你为什么要嫁给格伦
Don't worry. I mean, I told him why you were marrying him.
你干嘛跟他提起这个?
Why did you tell him I was marrying him?
因为你爱他呀...
Because you love him.
还因为...
And, you know, because...
因为嫁给格伦你会有经济保障
because with Glenn, you'll have security.
但那不是我要嫁给他的原因
But that's not why I'm marrying him.
那你是为什么?
Then why are you?
# I don't wanna be Ionely, baby #
# Please help me #
# I wanna love you all over #
# Do you believe in love? #
# Do you believe in love... #
嗨,露茜,你好吗
Hi, Rosie. How are you?
很好,亲爱的
Oh, fine, dear.
罗比在吗?我有点东西要给他
Is Robbie here? I came by to give him something.
不,茱莉娅,他不在这儿
Oh, no, Julia. I'm afraid he's not.
可今天是星期四
Yeah, but it's Thursday.
你有唱歌课的啊
You guys have your singing lessons today.
已经没有了
Not anymore.
他现在要去城里找份好工作...
Now that he's gone to the city to get a real job...
没时间再给我上课
he doesn't have time to give me lessons.
你凭什么觉得自己 会是个好的银行职员呢?
Why do you think you'd be a good hire for this bank?
我会努力工作...
Well, I'm ready to work hard...
我只要专心致志干一件事就能把它干好
and when I put my mind to something, I go all the way.
我会为你好好干的,先生
I'll go all the way for you, sir.
你有过实践经验吗?
Do you have any experience?
没有,但我是个大财迷
No, sir, I have no experience, but I'm a big fan of money.
我喜欢钱,要用钱,我的钱很少
I like it. I use it. I have a little.
我不断地把钱存进冰箱上的一个瓶子里
I keep it in a jar on top of my refrigerator.
我希望能多放些进去
I'd like to put more in that jar.
所以你来了这
That's where you come in.
他想挣钱
He wants to make money.
住进一幢
You know, live in a nice house...
窗子大灯也大的漂亮房子
with wide windows and lamps.
你总不能让他 一辈子和他姐姐住在一起...
You can't expect him to live forever with his sister...
那里挤得一塌糊涂
and the nipple-twisting that goes on there.
谢谢你抽时间上这来
Well, I thank you for your time.
实际上,先生, 我需要这份工作来吸引一个姑娘
Actually, sir, I really need this job to impress a girl.
请你离开好吗?
Will you leave now, please?
你不必直接给我这份工作
You don't even have to give me the job.
如果你能给我一些你的名片...
If you could just give me some business cards with my name on it...
我想那可能会有帮助
I think that might help.
我会尽量找到他,行吗?
OK, well, I'm gonna try and go look for him, OK?
告诉他我会给他加薪
Tell him I'll give him a raise.
一节课三个肉丸
Three meatballs a lesson.
这样行不行? 十节音乐课...
How about this? I'll give you ten singing lessons...
换一张名片.求你了
for one business card. Please.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
# The best things in life are free #
# But you can give them to the birds and bees #
# I want money #
# That's what I want #
嘿,茱莉娅,来这有什么事吗?
Hey, Julia. What are you doing here?
我去过露茜家找你
I went by Rosie's to find you.
我不再给人上课了
Oh? I'm not doing that anymore.
我觉得给人上课
I know. I just thought that teaching...
是你生活中的一个重要部分
was such a big part of your life.
过去是,但现在我得做些什么...
Well, it was, but now I'm doing some stuff...
来改善我的处境
to better my situation.
听起来有点自私
That sounds kind of selfish.
这不是自私
It's not selfish.
那里有很多钱 我要努力去捞上一些
There's a lot of money out there. I'm trying to get my hands on some.
但你不会想成为又一个雅皮白痴吧?
Yeah, but you don't want to be just another yuppie idiot.
怎么?那有什么不对呢?
Why? What's wrong with that?
不想再住在我姐姐的地下室里
Don't want to live in my sister's basement anymore.
我想要幢大房子和一些值钱的证券
I want to get a big house, have some security.
不能再把所有的时间用来帮助别人...
Can't do that doing favors for people all the time...
得到肉丸作报酬
getting paid in meatballs.
可你并不是那样现实的人
But you're above all that material bullshit.
我不知道,我们生活在一个物质世界...
I don't know. We're living in a material world...
大家都是物质男女
and I am a material girl. Or boy.
不,你不是
No, you're not.
那你呢?你不就对物质感兴趣吗?
What about you? You're into material shit.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
你嫁给格伦就是因为他有钱啊
What do I mean? You're marrying Glenn 'cause he's got money.
混蛋
You asshole.
哦,见鬼,这是她给我做的礼物
Oh, my God. She made me a present.
我真是个混球
I am an asshole!
你要去疯人院了
You're going to the mental institution.
滚开
Beat it!
# Go #
# How about it? #
# Got a wife and kids in Baltimore, Jack... #
鲁迪
Rudy.
照旧吗?
Same?
照样再来一杯
Give me the same, please.
# Like a river that don't know where it's flowin'... #
-怎么了? -给他一杯
- What's up? - There he is.
你没事吧?
- You all right? - Mm-hmm.
你知道吗? 你是对的,你一直都是对的
You know something? You were right. You've always been right.
什么我一直都是对的?
What have I been so right about?
女人,你只能和她们寻开心
Women. You just have fun with them.
一旦你投入感情,结果就会...
You get emotionally involved, and they end up, they...
她们会怎么对待你?
What do they do to you?
她们会撕碎你的心
They rip your heart out of your ass.
没错
That's right.
你和茱莉娅怎么了?
Did, uh, something happen with Julia?
我去了那个四人约会,明白吗?
I went on that double date, right?
但她要嫁的那个蠢货...
And the moron she's gonna marry...
竟然告诉我他在欺骗她
actually tells me he cheats on her.
可我能告诉她吗?
But can I tell her?
不,我凭什么去破坏别人的婚姻呢?
No. I mean, who am I to break up her marriage?
你需要一个妓女
You need a prostitute.
反正...
Anyways...
我很困惑
I'm confused.
因为你喜欢她
Well, because you like her.
我想我爱上她了
I think I'm in love with her.
但是我得让自己忘掉这念头,你懂吗?
But I gotta get that out of my head, you know?
以后我要象你一样
From now on, I'm just... I'm gonna be like you, man.
每天晚上找不同的女孩...
I'm just gonna be with a different chick every night...
过后再把她们打发走
and then I'll send them packin'.
听起来你似乎全想通了
Sounds like you got it all figured out.
我会给她们钱坐车回家...
I mean, I'm gonna have to give them cab money to go home...
因为不这样我会觉得不安... 但之后就只要说"再见,新娘"啦
because I'll feel bad if I don't, but after that, it's bye-bye, birdie.
再见
Bye-bye.
就这要,老兄,从现在起
That's it, man, starting right now.
我们要自由开心地...
Me and you are gonna be free and happy...
过下半辈子
the rest of our lives.
# Love my way #
# It's a new road #
我并不开心,我很痛苦
I'm not happy. I'm miserable.
什么?
Wha-What?
我小时候崇拜
See, I grew up idolizing guys...
象冯兹和文尼-巴巴里罗那样的男人
like Fonzie and Vinnie Barbarino...
因为他们能泡到许多妞
'cause they got a lot of chicks.
你知道他们俩怎么样了吗?
You know what happened to Fonzie and Vinnie Barbarino?
我听说冯兹想做导演...
Yeah. I read that Fonzie wants to be a director...
而巴巴里罗演了一部机械警探电影
and Barbarino, I think, the mechanical bull movie.
我还没看过
I didn't see it yet.
他们的作品被取消了
Their shows got canceled...
因为没人想看五十的老家伙
'cause no one wants to see a fifty-year-old guy...
还想泡小妞
hitting on chicks.
你说什么?
Then, what are you saying?
我在说我真正想要的是...
What I'm saying is, all I really want...
有人搂着我...
is someone to hold me...
并且告诉我一切都会好起来的
and tell me that everything is gonna be all right.
一切都会好起来的
Everything is gonna be all right.
# I fall low... #
如果你找到一个值得去爱的人...
If you found someone you can love...
就不要放她走
you can't let her get away.
# Love my way... #
你是对的,伙计,谢谢你,山米
You're right, man. Thank you, Sammy.
别告诉任何人我说过什么
Don't tell anyone what I said.
妈妈
- Mom. - Uh-huh?
你真正喜欢格伦吗?
Do you really like Glenn?
哦,当然,宝贝,干嘛不喜欢呢?
Oh, sure, honey. What's not to like?
他富有,迷人,大方...
He's rich, he's charming, he's handsome...
而且他现在拥有一切,因为他得到了你
and now he's really got it all 'cause he's got you.
宝贝,怎么了?
Honey, what's the matter?
我不知道自己是否还爱他
I don't know if I'm in love with him anymore.
为什么?
Why?
出了什么事?
What happened?
我不知道他是否真正适合我
I just don't know if he's the right guy for me.
我很多时间是和...
And I've been spending a lot of time...
另外的男人在一起, 罗比-哈特
with this other man, Robbie Hart.
那个婚礼歌手?
Ha. The wedding singer?
你想为了那个婚礼歌手离开格伦?
You're thinking of leaving Glenn for the wedding singer?
我不知道自己在想什么
I don't know what I'm thinking.
我很困惑
I'm confused.
我知道,宝贝
Oh, I know, sweetie.
你这是典型的"临婚退缩"心理
You've got what is known as the jitters...
每个人都会有
cold feet. Everybody has 'em.
我也有过
I had 'em.
当然,我应该尖叫着落荒而逃...
Course, I should have run screaming down the street...
要好过嫁给你父亲
instead of marrying your father...
但格伦不一样 他有责任感
but Glenn, he's different. He's a keeper.
你会在星期天和格伦结婚
You're gonna marry Glenn on Sunday.
你会爱他...
You're gonna love him...
一切都会很美妙
and everything's gonna be wonderful.
你的面纱在哪?在楼下
Where's your veil? Oh, it's downstairs.
我去拿
I'll go get it.
嗨,幸会
Hi. Nice to meet you.
我是格伦-古力亚太太
I'm Mrs. Glenn Gulia.
你好,幸会
Hello. It's nice to meet you.
我叫茱莉娅-古力亚
I'm Julia Gulia.
茱莉娅-古力亚
Julia Gulia.
我早上醒来的时候...
Right when I wake up in the morning...
第一个想到的就是你
you're the first person that pops in my head...
我一直不停地想着你
and I keep thinking about you over and over.
幸会
It's nice to meet you.
我是茱莉娅-古力亚太太
I'm Mrs. Julia Gulia.
Hi.
很高兴认识你
I'm pleased to meet you.
我是罗比-哈特太太
I'm Mrs. Robbie Hart.
我们很高兴你来参加我们的婚礼
Robbie and I are so pleased you could come to our wedding.
# Wikki-wikki-wikki-wikki, shut up #
# Wikki-wikki-wikki-wikki #
# Three words to the whack, step yourself back #
# You're gettin' down and then you're givin' no slack #
# Like a Burger King with a sack of Big Macs #
# You're throwin' down with the radical sacks #
Yeah. Word.
很不错是吧?
Pretty good, eh?
# You gotta funk it up until it knocks you down #
怎么样了?
What happened?
她看起来很高兴
She just looked way too happy.
我说不出口
I couldn't do it.
真遗憾,伙计
I'm sorry, man.
嘿,鲁迪,给罗比来杯双份的
Hey, Rudy. Get Robbie a double.
其实,鲁迪,不用你操心
Actually, Rudy, don't even worry about it.
我自己带了
I brought my own.
你不能在这喝
You can't drink that in here, Robbie.
那好吧 我去巷子里喝完它
All right. I'll finish up in the alley.
你们来不来?
Are you guys coming?
是那个婚礼歌手
Hey. It's the wedding singer.
嘿,格伦,怎么了?
Hey, Glenn. What's up?
我听说你没和霍莉办完事
Hey, Robbie, I heard you couldn't close the deal with Holly.
是怎么回事,你不会...
Yeah. What's the matter with that? You're not...
你喜欢女人,对吧?
You like women, right?
恐怕没你那么喜欢
Not as much as you do, I guess.
我们要去开一个小型的告别单身聚会
Listen, we're gonna have a little pre-bachelor party party.
你愿意来喝杯啤酒吗?
You want to come in and have a beer?
你太荒唐了,伙计
You're ridiculous, man.
停止这种欺骗行为吧,笨蛋
Stop all this cheating shit, moron.
她是个好姑娘
She's a good girl.
嘿,傻瓜...
Hey, asswipe...
别告诉茱莉娅这些事
don't go snitchin' to Julia about this.
我知道你对她有点着迷...
I know you got some little crush on her...
但你得面对现实
but you gotta face the facts.
她更愿意和一个真正的男人上床...
She'd rather go to bed with a real man...
而不是可怜的卖唱孤儿
not some poor singing orphan.
好吧,蠢货
All right, shithead.
自从五年级以后我还没打过架呢
I haven't been in a fight since I was in the fifth grade...
那小子让我揍出屎来了...
but I beat the shit out of that kid...
现在我要把你揍出屎来
so now I'm gonna beat the shit out of you.
你干什么?
OK, what are you doing, man?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我以前非常有劲呢
I used to be much stronger.
你死定了,伙计
You're dead, buddy.
Yeah! Yeah!
Hey.
你干嘛不为这事写首歌?
Why don't you write a song about this?
可以取名叫...
You can call it, uh...
"我的鼻子挨了一下...
I Got Punched in the Nose...
"因为我多管闲事"
For Stickin' my Face in Other People's Business.
走吧
Way to go.
听起来象首乡村歌曲
Sounds like a country song.
罗比
Hi, Robbie.
去死吧
Kiss my grits.
# I am the son #
# And the heir... #
我知道你喝醉了
I can see that you're drunk...
但没关系
and that's OK.
我还是要对你说
I'm still gonna tell you this.
我很想你,我想回到你身边
I really miss you, and I want to come back.
我不想再孤独了
I don't wanna be alone anymore.
不会的
No.
你不再孤独了
You're not alone anymore.
琳达回来了
Linda's back.
需要帮忙吗?
Can I help you?
罗比在吗?
Is Robbie here?
恐怕他有点不舒服
I'm afraid he's, uh, indisposed.
在洗澡
Shower.
你一定是琳达
You must be Linda.
对,是我...
Yeah, that's me...
罗比的未婚妻
Robbie's fiancee.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是茱莉娅-沙利文
I'm Julia Sullivan.
告诉他我来看过他好吗?
Would you tell him that I came by to see him?
哦,好的,没问题,珍妮佛
Oh, yeah, surely will, Jennifer.
是茱莉娅
It's Julia.
醒醒,懒虫
Wake up, sleepy head.
这是我们重新开始的第一天
This is the first day of our new life together.
叫醒我...
# Wake me up #
在你走之前
# Before you go-go #
不要留下我孤零零一个
# Don't leave me hanging on like a solo #
琳达?
- Linda? - Hi.
你在这干什么?
What are you doing here?
你晕倒了,所以我来照顾你
Well, you passed out, so I took care of you.
什么?你干嘛要照顾我?
What? Why'd you take care of me?
我昨晚跟你说过,我知道我错了...
I told you last night, Robbie, I realized I was wrong...
而且我想好好照顾你
and I want to take care of you for good.
我能学会面对你是婚礼歌手
I can learn to deal with the fact that you're just a wedding singer...
而不是摇滚歌星的现实 我甚至可以...
and not a rock star. I could even learn to deal...
你能学会接受这事?
You can learn to deal with that?
我可不想要你学着接受这事
I don't want you to learn to deal with that.
那不是什么好职业
That's not how it works.
天呐
Jeez!
罗比
Well, Robbie...
也许我们该等你感觉好些后再谈这事
maybe we should talk about this when you're feeling better.
嘿,神经病... 对于这事我的感觉没法好起来
Hey, psycho, I'm not gonna feel better about this.
结束了
It's over.
现在请把我的 "范海伦"(著名乐队)T恤脱下来...
Now please get out of my Van Halen T-shirt...
趁你这扫帚星还没拆散他们之前
before you jinx the band and they break up.
Oh, OK.
看来你还在为婚礼的事生气
So you're still pissed about that wedding thing.
格伦
Glenn.
格伦,早上好
Glenn, good morning.
早上好
Hi. Good morning.
Good morning. Hello.
嘿,宝贝
Hey, baby.
你想在床上做早餐吗?
You gonna make breakfast in bed?
哦,不
Um, no.
实际是我有一些想法...
Actually, I've been doing some thinking, and...
我不需要一个铺张的婚礼...
I don't need a big wedding...
我觉得之前我太自私了...
and I think that I've been really selfish...
让你做一些你不愿意做的事
in making you do something that you don't even want to do.
你想要去维加斯?
You wanna go to Vegas?
Yeah.
没问题,我们就去
Well, all right. Let's go.
Heh heh heh.
钟儿
# There were bells #
在山上
# On a hill #
但我从未听到它们的声音
# But I never heard them ringing #
没有,我一点也没听到...
# No, I never heard them at all #
直到有了你
# 'Til there was you #
Aww.
还有这乐曲...
# And there was music #
和这美丽的玫瑰花
# And there were wonderful roses #
它们告诉我...
# They tell me #
在黎明
# In sweet #
带着露珠
# Fragrant meadows #
甜美芬芳的草地上
# Of dawn and dew #
有爱...
# There was love #
围绕在四周...
# All around... #
1156次航班已做好登机准备...
Flight number 1156 is now ready for boarding.
We'd like to ask those passengers...
traveling with small children...
我从没听到过...
# No, I never heard it at all #
直到有了
# 'Til there was #
你
# You #
我总是想象理想的对象...
I just always envisioned the right one...
是我能与之偕老的人
being someone I could grow old with.
我明白,我就去取车
I know. I'll go get the car.
露茜,恭喜你
Rosie, congratulations.
有些事我必须重视,对吗?
I gotta go take care of something, OK?
我知道你会的,去找她
I know you do. Go get her.
好的
All right. All right.
-我想跟你谈谈 -我现在没空
- Robbie, I need to talk to you. - I can't talk right now.
你和琳达和好了?
Are you back with Linda?
没有,谁说的?
No. Why? Who said that?
茱莉娅,她去过你家...
Julia. She went to your house...
想跟你说她爱上了你...
to tell you she was falling for you...
结果是琳达穿着内衣开的门
and Linda answered the door in her underwear.
她非常失望...
She was so upset...
和格伦乘飞机去维加斯了
she and Glenn just jumped a plane to Vegas.
你说什么?他们不是明天结婚吗?
What do you mean? They're getting married tomorrow.
显然那还不够早
Well, apparently, that wasn't soon enough.
# I said, hip, hop #
# A-hippie to the hippie to the hip, hip, hop #
# You don't stop rockin' to the bang, bang boogie #
# Say, up comes the boogie #
# To the rhythm of the boogie that beats #
We're now ready for our general boarding.
亲爱的,准备好了吗?
That's it, sweetie. Ready to go?
Yeah.
这是个好主意, 很高兴你能改变主意
This is a great idea. I'm glad you came around.
你是想马上去赌一把开开心...
You want to do some gambling and have some fun right away...
还是只想结婚?
or you just want to get married?
我只想结婚
I just want to get married.
你决不可能找到她
You're never going to find her.
维加斯有无数的婚礼教堂
There's got to be a million wedding chapels in Vegas.
-谁有笔吗? -干什么?
- Does anybody have a pen? - What for?
我想到了一首好歌
I got a good idea for a song.
-给 -谢谢
- Here. - Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
对不起
Hey, I'm sorry.
需要效劳吗?
Can I help you?
请给我一张去维加斯的机票
Yeah. I need a ticket for Las Vegas, please.
我们只有一个...
We only have one seat left...
头等舱的座位了
and it's in our first-class section.
下一趟航班要等到早上
The next flight leaves in the morning.
可以借用你的信用卡吗?
Can I borrow your credit card?
你得还给我,好吗?
You're going to pay me back, right?
不,不过如果你不给我的话...
No, but if you don't give it to me...
我会把你在酒吧说的话告诉所有人
I'm going to tell everybody what you said at the bar.
谢啦
Thanks.
你真是太好了
Hey, that was really nice of you.
多谢
Thanks.
你喜欢"海鸥成群"这首歌吗?
Hey, do you like Flock of Seagulls?
我能看出你喜欢
I can see you do.
-祝我好运吧 -去找到她
- Wish me luck. - Go get her!
嘿,格伦,可以和我换个位子...
Hey, Glenn, do you mind if we switched seats...
让我坐靠窗的位子吗?
and I sat in the window seat?
我讨厌过道位子
Mmm. I hate the aisle seat.
每次手推车经过都会撞到我的手肘
Every time that drink cart comes by, it bangs me in the elbows.
你的手臂比我的小,茱莉娅
Your arms are smaller than mine, Jules.
我知道,可是我从没见过维加斯的夜景
I know. I just never saw the bright lights of Vegas before.
这样吧
Tell you what.
我们飞过机场时我让你靠着我怎么样?
How about I let you lean over me when we fly over the strip?
可以吗?
OK?
谢谢
Thank you.
热毛巾
Hot towel?
谢谢
Thanks.
Ah.
哦,老天
Oh, my.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
我以前从没坐过头等舱
I've never been on first class before.
我叫乔伊丝,有什么需要请尽管吩咐
My name is Joyce. Just buzz if you need anything.
谢谢你
Thank you.
给
Here.
谢谢
Thank you.
先生?
Sir?
那是比利偶像吗?
Is that Billy Idol?
-我相信是 -哦,我的天
- I believe it is. - Oh, my God.
你想要点香槟或橙汁吗
Would you like some champagne or some orange juice?
-要多少钱? -是免费的
- How much is it? - It's free.
什么?老天 真是难以置信
It's what? Holy shit, this is incredible.
不过我不能喝 我爱上的姑娘...
Actually, I shouldn't drink. I fell in love with this girl...
要嫁给一个白痴了...
and she's going to marry an idiot...
我要去维加斯阻止他们
so I'm on my way to Vegas to stop them.
这是我听说过的最美妙的事
That's the sweetest thing I've ever heard.
他们在哪结婚?
Where are they getting married?
我不知道在哪...
That's the problem... I don't know where...
但我一定会找到他们
but I'm going to run around and find them, you know?
我想做什么就一定能做到
I got to do what I got to do.
Oh.
下次经过时替我拿听饮料
Next time they come by, grab me a Heineken, will you?
她来告诉我她的感觉...
She comes over to tell me how she feels...
但是是琳达开的门...
and Linda answers the door...
除了我的"范海伦"T恤就什么都没穿
wearing nothing but my Van Halen T-shirt.
离谱
No way.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.
她要结婚了,而他会毁了她的生活
She's getting married, and he's going to ruin her life.
格伦配不上她
Ah, Glenn doesn't deserve her.
他只关心财产...
All he cares about are possessions...
靓车,CD机
fancy cars, CD players.
女人对他来说也是财产
Even women are possessions to him.
比利偶像都能明白
See? Billy Idol gets it.
我不知道她怎么会不明白
I don't know why she doesn't get it.
但愿你能找到她
Oh, I hope you find her.
你们肯定不会相信
You guys will not believe this.
经济舱有个可怜虫 以为自己是唐-约翰逊(影星)...
Some creep in coach who thinks he's Don Johnson...
要我加入"空中高潮俱乐部"
just asked me to be part of the mile-high club.
他说我是一流顶级的美味
He said I was grade-A, top-choice meat.
他就在这吗?
- Is he right in here? - Yeah.
什么是"空中高潮俱乐部"?
What's the mile-high club?
我的天,那家伙正是格伦
Oh, my God. The mile-high guy is Glenn.
-他们就在这架飞机上 -不行
- They're on this plane. - No way!
你们得帮帮我
You guys got to help me.
没问题
Right!
太棒了
Yeah!
下午好,各位
Good afternoon, everyone.
我们正从26000尺高空
We're flying at 26,000 feet...
向30000尺爬升
moving up to 30,000 feet...
我们去维加斯的途中是一片晴空
and we got clear skies all the way to Las Vegas.
现在,我们将给大家送上飞行中的娱乐
And right now, we're bringing you some in-flight entertainment.
我们头等舱的一个乘客...
One of our first-class passengers...
将为你们送上一首歌...
would like to sing you a song...
其灵感来自我们经济舱的一位乘客
inspired by one of our coach passengers.
而我们向来都会满足头等舱乘客的...
And since we let our first-class passengers...
任何要求...
do pretty much whatever they want...
有请
here he is.
当你忧伤的时候...
# I wanna make you smile #
我要让你欢笑...
# Whenever you're sad #
当你关节痛时...
# Carry you around #
带你四处走走
# When your arthritis is bad #
我想要的只是...
# Oh, all I wanna do #
和你一起变老
# Is grow old with you #
当你肚子疼时...
# I'll get you medicine #
我会替你拿药...
# When your tummy aches #
如果壁炉坏了...
# Build you a fire #
我会做个新的
# If the furnace breaks #
噢,和你一起变老
# Oh, it could be so nice #
该是多么美妙
# Growin' old with you #
我会想念你...
# I'll miss you #
亲吻你...
# Kiss you #
你冷的时候
# Give you my coat #
给你我的外套
# When you are cold #
需要你...
# Need you #
满足你...
# Feed you #
甚至由你摆布...
# Even let you hold #
遥控
# The remote control #
那傻瓜到底在这干什么?
What the hell's that fruit doing here?
让开路
Get out... get out of the way!
抱歉,先生,我必须给大家提供饮料
Excuse me, sir. I have to serve the beverages.
Oh!
你好啊,先生,要鸡还是鱼?
How you doing, sir? Chicken or fish?
别挡路,不然有你好受的
You better get out of my way, Billy, or you're going to get hurt.
哦,是吗?
Oh, yeah?
不要这样和比利偶像说话
Don't you talk to Billy Idol that way.
Uhh!
让我在厨房的水槽里
# So let me clear the dishes #
洗盘子
# In our kitchen sink #
当你喝得太多时
# Put you to bed #
把你放到床上
# When you've had too much to drink #
# Oh #
我可以成为
# I could be the man #
与你偕老的男人
# Who grows old with you #
我想要和你
# I wanna grow old #
一起变老
# With you #
这是最美妙的歌
That was the most beautiful song.
我必须承认
I got a confession to make.
这首歌是写给你的
That song was about you.
Good.
我爱你
I'm in love with you.
我也很爱你
I am so in love with you.
Aww.
这首歌不错
Hey, Robbie, that wasn't a bad song.
我会跟发行公司的人说说你的事
You know, I'm going to tell those record company guys about you.
不介意我先给她一个吻吧?
You mind if I give her a kiss first?
做你想做的事吧
Oh, yeah. Do what you got to do.
# Ah ha ha ha #
# Ha #
我知道这种事...
# I know this #
很多这种事...
# Much is true #
# Ah ha ha ha #
# Ha ha #
是真的
# I know this #
我知道这种事...
# Much is true #
# Ah ha ha ha #
我知道......
# I know, I know, I know #
很多都是真的
# This much is true #
哦,是的,我知道...
# Oh, yes, I do #
罗比和茱莉娅
# Robbie and Julia #
# Ha ha #
# I heard you on my wireless back in '52 #
# Lying awake, intent at tuning in on you #
# If I was young, it didn't stop you comin' through #
# Oh-a oh #
# They took the credit for your second symphony #
# Rewritten by machine, our new technology #
# And now I understand the supernova scene #
# Oh-a oh #
# I met your children #
# What did you tell them? #
# Video killed the radio star #
# In my mind and in my car #
# We can't rewind, we've gone too far #
# Oh oh oh oh oh #
# And now we meet in an abandoned studio #
# You hear the playback, and it seems so long ago #
# And you remembered the jingles used to go #
# Oh-a oh #
# You were the first one #
# You were the last one #
# Video killed the radio star #
# 'Cause in my mind and in my car #
# We can't rewind, we've gone too far #
# Too far! #
# Oh oh oh oh #
# Oh oh oh oh oh #
# All right #
# Video killed the radio star #
# 'Cause in my mind and in my car #
# We can't rewind, we've gone too far #
# Pictures came and broke your heart #
# So put all the blame on VCRs #
# You are #
# A radio star #
# Video killed the radio star #
# Video killed that radio star #
# Yes, it did #
# Video killed the radio star #
# 'Cause in my mind and in my car #
# We can't rewind, we've gone too far #
# Pictures came and broke your heart #
# So put all the blame on VCRs #
# You are #
# A radio star #
# Video killed the radio star #
# Video killed that radio star #